{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645541363","data":{"timestamp":" 947645541363"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645544795","data":{"timestamp":" 947645544795"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645545752","data":{"timestamp":" 947645545752"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645549343","data":{"timestamp":" 947645549343"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645550787","data":{"timestamp":" 947645550787"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645550961","data":{"timestamp":" 947645550961"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645551363","data":{"timestamp":" 947645551363"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645551433","data":{"timestamp":" 947645551433"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645553991","data":{"timestamp":" 947645553991"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645555380","data":{"timestamp":" 947645555379"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645556851","data":{"timestamp":" 947645556851"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645557532","data":{"timestamp":" 947645557532"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645562453","data":{"timestamp":" 947645562453"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645563668","data":{"timestamp":" 947645563668"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645565464","data":{"timestamp":" 947645565464"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645566481","data":{"timestamp":" 947645566481"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645568367","data":{"timestamp":" 947645568367"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645570332","data":{"timestamp":" 947645570332"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645571819","data":{"timestamp":" 947645571819"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645579581","data":{"timestamp":" 947645579581"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645581300","data":{"timestamp":" 947645581300"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645587789","data":{"timestamp":" 947645587788"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645589125","data":{"timestamp":" 947645589125"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645591040","data":{"timestamp":" 947645591040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645591808","data":{"timestamp":" 947645591808"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645600220","data":{"timestamp":" 947645600219"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645612148","data":{"timestamp":" 947645612148"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645618269","data":{"timestamp":" 947645618269"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645619499","data":{"timestamp":" 947645619499"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645623289","data":{"timestamp":" 947645623289"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645625692","data":{"timestamp":" 947645625691"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645627583","data":{"timestamp":" 947645627583"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645628564","data":{"timestamp":" 947645628564"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645630508","data":{"timestamp":" 947645630507"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645632366","data":{"timestamp":" 947645632363"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645637914","data":{"timestamp":" 947645637914"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645643847","data":{"timestamp":" 947645643847"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645645229","data":{"timestamp":" 947645645229"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645645235","data":{"timestamp":" 947645645234"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645646304","data":{"timestamp":" 947645646304"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645651295","data":{"timestamp":" 947645651295"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645653118","data":{"timestamp":" 947645653118"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645657697","data":{"timestamp":" 947645657697"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645668374","data":{"timestamp":" 947645668374"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645669053","data":{"timestamp":" 947645669053"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645670058","data":{"timestamp":" 947645670058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645673871","data":{"timestamp":" 947645673871"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645674477","data":{"timestamp":" 947645674477"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645676318","data":{"timestamp":" 947645676317"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645681055","data":{"timestamp":" 947645681055"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645682911","data":{"timestamp":" 947645682911"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645684574","data":{"timestamp":" 947645684574"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" START_MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645688917","data":{"timestamp":" 947645688917"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645690578","data":{"timestamp":" 947645690578"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645696630","data":{"timestamp":" 947645696630"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645707535","data":{"timestamp":" 947645707534"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645709230","data":{"timestamp":" 947645709230"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645712770","data":{"timestamp":" 947645712770"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645718490","data":{"timestamp":" 947645718490"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645723943","data":{"timestamp":" 947645723943"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" START_WALIRUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645725619","data":{"timestamp":" 947645725617"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645726897","data":{"timestamp":" 947645726897"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645726901","data":{"timestamp":" 947645726901"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" WAMEBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645727589","data":{"timestamp":" 947645727589"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645727592","data":{"timestamp":" 947645727592"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645728721","data":{"timestamp":" 947645728721"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645736635","data":{"timestamp":" 947645736635"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645742488","data":{"timestamp":" 947645742488"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645744195","data":{"timestamp":" 947645744195"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645745819","data":{"timestamp":" 947645745819"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645748418","data":{"timestamp":" 947645748417"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645749836","data":{"timestamp":" 947645749835"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645756058","data":{"timestamp":" 947645756058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" START_WAMEBEBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645757799","data":{"timestamp":" 947645757799"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645759469","data":{"timestamp":" 947645759469"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645764292","data":{"timestamp":" 947645764292"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645769965","data":{"timestamp":" 947645769965"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645772062","data":{"timestamp":" 947645772062"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645772851","data":{"timestamp":" 947645772851"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645781254","data":{"timestamp":" 947645781254"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645781793","data":{"timestamp":" 947645781793"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645783251","data":{"timestamp":" 947645783250"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645785274","data":{"timestamp":" 947645785273"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645789259","data":{"timestamp":" 947645789259"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645790905","data":{"timestamp":" 947645790905"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645791664","data":{"timestamp":" 947645791664"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645795185","data":{"timestamp":" 947645795185"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645796858","data":{"timestamp":" 947645796858"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645798037","data":{"timestamp":" 947645798037"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645799525","data":{"timestamp":" 947645799525"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" ALIDONDOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645800603","data":{"timestamp":" 947645800603"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645800606","data":{"timestamp":" 947645800606"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" MATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645802746","data":{"timestamp":" 947645802746"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645803714","data":{"timestamp":" 947645803714"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645807223","data":{"timestamp":" 947645807223"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645809107","data":{"timestamp":" 947645809105"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645811600","data":{"timestamp":" 947645811600"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645813607","data":{"timestamp":" 947645813607"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645815481","data":{"timestamp":" 947645815481"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645817330","data":{"timestamp":" 947645817330"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645820724","data":{"timestamp":" 947645820724"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645822453","data":{"timestamp":" 947645822452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645824518","data":{"timestamp":" 947645824517"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645826583","data":{"timestamp":" 947645826583"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645828174","data":{"timestamp":" 947645828174"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645832556","data":{"timestamp":" 947645832555"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" START_ALIFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645834396","data":{"timestamp":" 947645834396"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645836336","data":{"timestamp":" 947645836336"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645838382","data":{"timestamp":" 947645838382"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645842706","data":{"timestamp":" 947645842705"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645844684","data":{"timestamp":" 947645844684"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645852581","data":{"timestamp":" 947645852581"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" START_AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645855527","data":{"timestamp":" 947645855527"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645864623","data":{"timestamp":" 947645864623"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" START_AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645865864","data":{"timestamp":" 947645865864"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645867635","data":{"timestamp":" 947645867635"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645871694","data":{"timestamp":" 947645871694"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645878112","data":{"timestamp":" 947645878112"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645882860","data":{"timestamp":" 947645882860"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIPAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645886391","data":{"timestamp":" 947645886391"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645888386","data":{"timestamp":" 947645888385"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645894168","data":{"timestamp":" 947645894168"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645894900","data":{"timestamp":" 947645894900"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645896516","data":{"timestamp":" 947645896515"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645900248","data":{"timestamp":" 947645900248"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645902144","data":{"timestamp":" 947645902144"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645902796","data":{"timestamp":" 947645902796"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645905948","data":{"timestamp":" 947645905948"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645907398","data":{"timestamp":" 947645907397"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645910573","data":{"timestamp":" 947645910573"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645912649","data":{"timestamp":" 947645912649"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645912653","data":{"timestamp":" 947645912653"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645912661","data":{"timestamp":" 947645912661"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645914509","data":{"timestamp":" 947645914508"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KIGAE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645920193","data":{"timestamp":" 947645920193"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645921697","data":{"timestamp":" 947645921697"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645922777","data":{"timestamp":" 947645922777"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645927023","data":{"timestamp":" 947645927023"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645929485","data":{"timestamp":" 947645929485"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645934049","data":{"timestamp":" 947645934049"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGAE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645937736","data":{"timestamp":" 947645937736"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645937827","data":{"timestamp":" 947645937826"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUNGU"," userResponse":" START_NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645941616","data":{"timestamp":" 947645941616"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUNGU"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645953372","data":{"timestamp":" 947645953372"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645953377","data":{"timestamp":" 947645953377"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645953506","data":{"timestamp":" 947645953506"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645954569","data":{"timestamp":" 947645954569"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KIGAE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645955954","data":{"timestamp":" 947645955954"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645957097","data":{"timestamp":" 947645957097"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KIGAE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645958689","data":{"timestamp":" 947645958689"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645960186","data":{"timestamp":" 947645960186"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645963429","data":{"timestamp":" 947645963429"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645965230","data":{"timestamp":" 947645965230"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645966516","data":{"timestamp":" 947645966516"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645967977","data":{"timestamp":" 947645967977"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645973144","data":{"timestamp":" 947645973144"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645975507","data":{"timestamp":" 947645975507"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645977311","data":{"timestamp":" 947645977310"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645980072","data":{"timestamp":" 947645980072"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645989469","data":{"timestamp":" 947645989469"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645990966","data":{"timestamp":" 947645990966"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645991327","data":{"timestamp":" 947645991327"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIPAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947645996734","data":{"timestamp":" 947645996734"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646004122","data":{"timestamp":" 947646004121"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646004805","data":{"timestamp":" 947646004805"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646006222","data":{"timestamp":" 947646006222"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646006981","data":{"timestamp":" 947646006981"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646007576","data":{"timestamp":" 947646007576"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646010695","data":{"timestamp":" 947646010694"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646013167","data":{"timestamp":" 947646013167"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" LIMEZIMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646015525","data":{"timestamp":" 947646015525"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646017864","data":{"timestamp":" 947646017864"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646018872","data":{"timestamp":" 947646018872"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646022816","data":{"timestamp":" 947646022815"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" START_WAKIMCHUKULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646024921","data":{"timestamp":" 947646024921"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646025981","data":{"timestamp":" 947646025981"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646031078","data":{"timestamp":" 947646031078"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646033679","data":{"timestamp":" 947646033679"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646033683","data":{"timestamp":" 947646033683"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646035111","data":{"timestamp":" 947646035110"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646037386","data":{"timestamp":" 947646037386"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646038845","data":{"timestamp":" 947646038845"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646039762","data":{"timestamp":" 947646039762"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646040777","data":{"timestamp":" 947646040777"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646041741","data":{"timestamp":" 947646041741"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646043543","data":{"timestamp":" 947646043542"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646045018","data":{"timestamp":" 947646045018"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646049166","data":{"timestamp":" 947646049166"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" USADIZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646051178","data":{"timestamp":" 947646051178"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646051955","data":{"timestamp":" 947646051955"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646054364","data":{"timestamp":" 947646054364"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646054370","data":{"timestamp":" 947646054370"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646055365","data":{"timestamp":" 947646055365"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646055663","data":{"timestamp":" 947646055662"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646065692","data":{"timestamp":" 947646065692"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646066780","data":{"timestamp":" 947646066780"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646068707","data":{"timestamp":" 947646068707"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646070520","data":{"timestamp":" 947646070520"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646072084","data":{"timestamp":" 947646072084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646074463","data":{"timestamp":" 947646074463"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646076604","data":{"timestamp":" 947646076603"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" LIMEZIMIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646078061","data":{"timestamp":" 947646078061"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646082960","data":{"timestamp":" 947646082960"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646088064","data":{"timestamp":" 947646088064"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646090027","data":{"timestamp":" 947646090027"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646092089","data":{"timestamp":" 947646092089"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646094477","data":{"timestamp":" 947646094477"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646095922","data":{"timestamp":" 947646095921"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646099726","data":{"timestamp":" 947646099725"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" MAKALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646117823","data":{"timestamp":" 947646117823"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646126875","data":{"timestamp":" 947646126875"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" START_ALIWASHUKURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646128871","data":{"timestamp":" 947646128871"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646129375","data":{"timestamp":" 947646129375"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646131027","data":{"timestamp":" 947646131027"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646132557","data":{"timestamp":" 947646132557"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646133833","data":{"timestamp":" 947646133833"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646138533","data":{"timestamp":" 947646138533"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" KUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646139791","data":{"timestamp":" 947646139791"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" START_KUHARAKISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646141595","data":{"timestamp":" 947646141595"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646142580","data":{"timestamp":" 947646142580"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646144336","data":{"timestamp":" 947646144336"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646152569","data":{"timestamp":" 947646152569"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646159246","data":{"timestamp":" 947646159246"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646160538","data":{"timestamp":" 947646160538"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646164440","data":{"timestamp":" 947646164440"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" START_KUFURAHIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646166339","data":{"timestamp":" 947646166339"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646171444","data":{"timestamp":" 947646171444"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" KUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646171448","data":{"timestamp":" 947646171448"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646190245","data":{"timestamp":" 947646190244"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646190415","data":{"timestamp":" 947646190414"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646190762","data":{"timestamp":" 947646190761"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646198133","data":{"timestamp":" 947646198133"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646200697","data":{"timestamp":" 947646200697"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" START_HALIKUTOSHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646202596","data":{"timestamp":" 947646202595"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646225948","data":{"timestamp":" 947646225948"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646231120","data":{"timestamp":" 947646231120"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" START_ALIRUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646232708","data":{"timestamp":" 947646232708"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646243302","data":{"timestamp":" 947646243302"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646243306","data":{"timestamp":" 947646243306"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646247119","data":{"timestamp":" 947646247118"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646248491","data":{"timestamp":" 947646248491"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646249824","data":{"timestamp":" 947646249824"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646250895","data":{"timestamp":" 947646250895"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646268683","data":{"timestamp":" 947646268683"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646270394","data":{"timestamp":" 947646270394"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646270427","data":{"timestamp":" 947646270427"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646271620","data":{"timestamp":" 947646271620"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646274259","data":{"timestamp":" 947646274258"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646276646","data":{"timestamp":" 947646276646"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646281088","data":{"timestamp":" 947646281088"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646283369","data":{"timestamp":" 947646283368"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646285052","data":{"timestamp":" 947646285051"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" START_AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646286913","data":{"timestamp":" 947646286913"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646287832","data":{"timestamp":" 947646287832"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" START_HALIKUTOSHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646289177","data":{"timestamp":" 947646289177"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646290604","data":{"timestamp":" 947646290604"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646292457","data":{"timestamp":" 947646292456"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646294361","data":{"timestamp":" 947646294361"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646296401","data":{"timestamp":" 947646296400"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646306443","data":{"timestamp":" 947646306443"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" START_MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646307966","data":{"timestamp":" 947646307966"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646308311","data":{"timestamp":" 947646308311"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646308315","data":{"timestamp":" 947646308315"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646315384","data":{"timestamp":" 947646315384"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_HALIKUTOSHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646320048","data":{"timestamp":" 947646320048"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646321654","data":{"timestamp":" 947646321653"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646322614","data":{"timestamp":" 947646322614"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646324324","data":{"timestamp":" 947646324324"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646325873","data":{"timestamp":" 947646325872"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646340084","data":{"timestamp":" 947646340084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646341759","data":{"timestamp":" 947646341759"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646354079","data":{"timestamp":" 947646354079"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646354493","data":{"timestamp":" 947646354493"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646356686","data":{"timestamp":" 947646356686"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" UNARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646356690","data":{"timestamp":" 947646356690"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646359294","data":{"timestamp":" 947646359294"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" START_KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646361597","data":{"timestamp":" 947646361597"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646363027","data":{"timestamp":" 947646363027"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646365588","data":{"timestamp":" 947646365588"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646368942","data":{"timestamp":" 947646368942"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646369732","data":{"timestamp":" 947646369732"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646372326","data":{"timestamp":" 947646372326"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646374510","data":{"timestamp":" 947646374510"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646375979","data":{"timestamp":" 947646375978"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646377577","data":{"timestamp":" 947646377577"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646378537","data":{"timestamp":" 947646378537"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646381197","data":{"timestamp":" 947646381197"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646382554","data":{"timestamp":" 947646382553"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646383512","data":{"timestamp":" 947646383511"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646386477","data":{"timestamp":" 947646386477"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646387458","data":{"timestamp":" 947646387458"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646390195","data":{"timestamp":" 947646390194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646390986","data":{"timestamp":" 947646390985"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" START_AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646392073","data":{"timestamp":" 947646392073"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646393627","data":{"timestamp":" 947646393627"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646395519","data":{"timestamp":" 947646395519"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646400004","data":{"timestamp":" 947646400004"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646402679","data":{"timestamp":" 947646402679"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646404960","data":{"timestamp":" 947646404960"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646406664","data":{"timestamp":" 947646406664"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646408497","data":{"timestamp":" 947646408497"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" NIKIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646414039","data":{"timestamp":" 947646414039"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646415240","data":{"timestamp":" 947646415239"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646418617","data":{"timestamp":" 947646418617"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646424447","data":{"timestamp":" 947646424446"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646427648","data":{"timestamp":" 947646427648"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646428438","data":{"timestamp":" 947646428438"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646433052","data":{"timestamp":" 947646433052"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646435060","data":{"timestamp":" 947646435059"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646439623","data":{"timestamp":" 947646439623"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646442302","data":{"timestamp":" 947646442302"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646443890","data":{"timestamp":" 947646443889"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646449056","data":{"timestamp":" 947646449056"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646456572","data":{"timestamp":" 947646456572"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" START_WALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646458580","data":{"timestamp":" 947646458580"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646461870","data":{"timestamp":" 947646461870"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646463023","data":{"timestamp":" 947646463023"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646464506","data":{"timestamp":" 947646464505"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646465623","data":{"timestamp":" 947646465622"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646467562","data":{"timestamp":" 947646467562"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646469094","data":{"timestamp":" 947646469094"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646470712","data":{"timestamp":" 947646470712"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646478168","data":{"timestamp":" 947646478168"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" START_AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646479522","data":{"timestamp":" 947646479522"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646480094","data":{"timestamp":" 947646480094"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646486530","data":{"timestamp":" 947646486530"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646488270","data":{"timestamp":" 947646488269"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646490957","data":{"timestamp":" 947646490957"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646497096","data":{"timestamp":" 947646497096"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" ALIRUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646498355","data":{"timestamp":" 947646498354"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646501737","data":{"timestamp":" 947646501737"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646502798","data":{"timestamp":" 947646502797"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646505370","data":{"timestamp":" 947646505370"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646506878","data":{"timestamp":" 947646506878"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646509987","data":{"timestamp":" 947646509987"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646512711","data":{"timestamp":" 947646512711"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646514385","data":{"timestamp":" 947646514385"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646515066","data":{"timestamp":" 947646515066"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646520786","data":{"timestamp":" 947646520786"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646522599","data":{"timestamp":" 947646522599"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646524085","data":{"timestamp":" 947646524084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646526765","data":{"timestamp":" 947646526765"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646531753","data":{"timestamp":" 947646531753"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646533132","data":{"timestamp":" 947646533132"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646534588","data":{"timestamp":" 947646534588"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646538040","data":{"timestamp":" 947646538040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646540128","data":{"timestamp":" 947646540128"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646548683","data":{"timestamp":" 947646548683"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646550648","data":{"timestamp":" 947646550648"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646553326","data":{"timestamp":" 947646553326"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646554298","data":{"timestamp":" 947646554298"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646557762","data":{"timestamp":" 947646557762"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646557884","data":{"timestamp":" 947646557884"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" dfd3d311-8bd9-4256-a482-bc0988b0bbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646575766","data":{"timestamp":" 947646575766"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646577405","data":{"timestamp":" 947646577405"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646580556","data":{"timestamp":" 947646580556"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646585572","data":{"timestamp":" 947646585572"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646586922","data":{"timestamp":" 947646586922"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646587745","data":{"timestamp":" 947646587744"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646591009","data":{"timestamp":" 947646591008"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646592768","data":{"timestamp":" 947646592768"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646593831","data":{"timestamp":" 947646593831"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646597624","data":{"timestamp":" 947646597624"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646598535","data":{"timestamp":" 947646598535"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646599857","data":{"timestamp":" 947646599857"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646601079","data":{"timestamp":" 947646601079"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646604859","data":{"timestamp":" 947646604859"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646606950","data":{"timestamp":" 947646606950"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646607044","data":{"timestamp":" 947646607044"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 27bdbbd8-371c-43e2-993a-6dd6e7290977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646621483","data":{"timestamp":" 947646621483"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646623201","data":{"timestamp":" 947646623200"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646624358","data":{"timestamp":" 947646624358"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646630173","data":{"timestamp":" 947646630173"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646634138","data":{"timestamp":" 947646634138"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646634968","data":{"timestamp":" 947646634968"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646636688","data":{"timestamp":" 947646636688"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646638762","data":{"timestamp":" 947646638762"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646639674","data":{"timestamp":" 947646639673"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646641758","data":{"timestamp":" 947646641757"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646642806","data":{"timestamp":" 947646642806"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646644884","data":{"timestamp":" 947646644884"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646663554","data":{"timestamp":" 947646663554"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646668203","data":{"timestamp":" 947646668202"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646673599","data":{"timestamp":" 947646673599"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646677152","data":{"timestamp":" 947646677151"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646678609","data":{"timestamp":" 947646678609"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646680018","data":{"timestamp":" 947646680017"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646682407","data":{"timestamp":" 947646682407"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646686315","data":{"timestamp":" 947646686315"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646687560","data":{"timestamp":" 947646687560"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646689506","data":{"timestamp":" 947646689505"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646690090","data":{"timestamp":" 947646690089"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646703481","data":{"timestamp":" 947646703481"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646708653","data":{"timestamp":" 947646708652"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646715689","data":{"timestamp":" 947646715689"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646718906","data":{"timestamp":" 947646718906"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646721040","data":{"timestamp":" 947646721040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646728194","data":{"timestamp":" 947646728194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646730385","data":{"timestamp":" 947646730385"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646734810","data":{"timestamp":" 947646734809"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646734918","data":{"timestamp":" 947646734918"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 5d90b9de-8948-4584-a33e-465f78e6440c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646744304","data":{"timestamp":" 947646744304"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646744526","data":{"timestamp":" 947646744526"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646745489","data":{"timestamp":" 947646745489"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646746761","data":{"timestamp":" 947646746761"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646749621","data":{"timestamp":" 947646749621"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646750464","data":{"timestamp":" 947646750464"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646750778","data":{"timestamp":" 947646750778"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646752011","data":{"timestamp":" 947646752011"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646755507","data":{"timestamp":" 947646755506"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646756489","data":{"timestamp":" 947646756489"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646756742","data":{"timestamp":" 947646756742"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646757684","data":{"timestamp":" 947646757684"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646760500","data":{"timestamp":" 947646760500"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646761533","data":{"timestamp":" 947646761533"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646762006","data":{"timestamp":" 947646762006"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646766525","data":{"timestamp":" 947646766525"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646766624","data":{"timestamp":" 947646766624"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 6fa09c79-d207-4c98-a445-ccd850bbfcf7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646795588","data":{"timestamp":" 947646795588"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646797253","data":{"timestamp":" 947646797253"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646801262","data":{"timestamp":" 947646801262"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646803626","data":{"timestamp":" 947646803626"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646805040","data":{"timestamp":" 947646805040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646806714","data":{"timestamp":" 947646806714"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646809078","data":{"timestamp":" 947646809078"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646811057","data":{"timestamp":" 947646811056"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646813066","data":{"timestamp":" 947646813066"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646813070","data":{"timestamp":" 947646813070"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646818958","data":{"timestamp":" 947646818958"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646821069","data":{"timestamp":" 947646821068"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646822516","data":{"timestamp":" 947646822515"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646827589","data":{"timestamp":" 947646827589"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646830015","data":{"timestamp":" 947646830015"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646831429","data":{"timestamp":" 947646831428"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646833251","data":{"timestamp":" 947646833251"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646834624","data":{"timestamp":" 947646834624"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646836440","data":{"timestamp":" 947646836440"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646839262","data":{"timestamp":" 947646839261"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646846969","data":{"timestamp":" 947646846968"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646849436","data":{"timestamp":" 947646849436"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646852608","data":{"timestamp":" 947646852608"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646855235","data":{"timestamp":" 947646855235"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646857161","data":{"timestamp":" 947646857161"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646861208","data":{"timestamp":" 947646861208"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646862540","data":{"timestamp":" 947646862540"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646866377","data":{"timestamp":" 947646866377"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646870634","data":{"timestamp":" 947646870634"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646876547","data":{"timestamp":" 947646876547"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646877980","data":{"timestamp":" 947646877980"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646879055","data":{"timestamp":" 947646879054"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646880901","data":{"timestamp":" 947646880899"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646884568","data":{"timestamp":" 947646884568"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646888889","data":{"timestamp":" 947646888889"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646890047","data":{"timestamp":" 947646890047"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646890753","data":{"timestamp":" 947646890752"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646893047","data":{"timestamp":" 947646893047"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646896953","data":{"timestamp":" 947646896953"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646898807","data":{"timestamp":" 947646898806"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646900091","data":{"timestamp":" 947646900091"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646900095","data":{"timestamp":" 947646900095"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646904391","data":{"timestamp":" 947646904391"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646904395","data":{"timestamp":" 947646904395"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646904399","data":{"timestamp":" 947646904399"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646910251","data":{"timestamp":" 947646910251"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646912028","data":{"timestamp":" 947646912028"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646913876","data":{"timestamp":" 947646913876"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646915026","data":{"timestamp":" 947646915025"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646917499","data":{"timestamp":" 947646917499"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646919134","data":{"timestamp":" 947646919134"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646920535","data":{"timestamp":" 947646920535"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646921885","data":{"timestamp":" 947646921885"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646922192","data":{"timestamp":" 947646922192"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646925524","data":{"timestamp":" 947646925524"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646926767","data":{"timestamp":" 947646926767"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646930383","data":{"timestamp":" 947646930383"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646934230","data":{"timestamp":" 947646934229"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646935897","data":{"timestamp":" 947646935896"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646937175","data":{"timestamp":" 947646937175"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646938864","data":{"timestamp":" 947646938864"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646941580","data":{"timestamp":" 947646941580"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646943228","data":{"timestamp":" 947646943228"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646945078","data":{"timestamp":" 947646945078"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646946845","data":{"timestamp":" 947646946845"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646948770","data":{"timestamp":" 947646948770"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646950803","data":{"timestamp":" 947646950803"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646952122","data":{"timestamp":" 947646952122"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646952805","data":{"timestamp":" 947646952805"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646954383","data":{"timestamp":" 947646954383"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646960256","data":{"timestamp":" 947646960256"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646962010","data":{"timestamp":" 947646962010"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646963695","data":{"timestamp":" 947646963694"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646967176","data":{"timestamp":" 947646967176"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646968388","data":{"timestamp":" 947646968388"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646970566","data":{"timestamp":" 947646970566"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646973468","data":{"timestamp":" 947646973467"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646976138","data":{"timestamp":" 947646976138"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646978225","data":{"timestamp":" 947646978225"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646980513","data":{"timestamp":" 947646980513"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646982080","data":{"timestamp":" 947646982080"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646983827","data":{"timestamp":" 947646983827"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646984116","data":{"timestamp":" 947646984116"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646984947","data":{"timestamp":" 947646984947"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646988037","data":{"timestamp":" 947646988037"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646989627","data":{"timestamp":" 947646989627"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646991282","data":{"timestamp":" 947646991282"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646991592","data":{"timestamp":" 947646991591"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646994534","data":{"timestamp":" 947646994533"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646996212","data":{"timestamp":" 947646996212"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947646998272","data":{"timestamp":" 947646998271"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647000722","data":{"timestamp":" 947647000722"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647002782","data":{"timestamp":" 947647002781"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647003359","data":{"timestamp":" 947647003359"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MATE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647005143","data":{"timestamp":" 947647005143"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647008440","data":{"timestamp":" 947647008440"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647010926","data":{"timestamp":" 947647010926"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647012467","data":{"timestamp":" 947647012466"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647014796","data":{"timestamp":" 947647014796"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647018981","data":{"timestamp":" 947647018981"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647019469","data":{"timestamp":" 947647019469"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647023280","data":{"timestamp":" 947647023280"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" START_ANGEWEZAJE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647025159","data":{"timestamp":" 947647025159"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647026457","data":{"timestamp":" 947647026456"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647030568","data":{"timestamp":" 947647030568"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647032442","data":{"timestamp":" 947647032442"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647032762","data":{"timestamp":" 947647032762"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647035089","data":{"timestamp":" 947647035089"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647037119","data":{"timestamp":" 947647037119"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647039821","data":{"timestamp":" 947647039821"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647041396","data":{"timestamp":" 947647041396"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647043579","data":{"timestamp":" 947647043579"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" START_ALIFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647045772","data":{"timestamp":" 947647045772"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647076088","data":{"timestamp":" 947647076088"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" START_AKAFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647082349","data":{"timestamp":" 947647082349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647084336","data":{"timestamp":" 947647084336"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647085694","data":{"timestamp":" 947647085694"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647088618","data":{"timestamp":" 947647088618"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647099947","data":{"timestamp":" 947647099947"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647101940","data":{"timestamp":" 947647101940"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647103901","data":{"timestamp":" 947647103901"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647106238","data":{"timestamp":" 947647106238"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647108750","data":{"timestamp":" 947647108749"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647111065","data":{"timestamp":" 947647111065"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647113200","data":{"timestamp":" 947647113200"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647115044","data":{"timestamp":" 947647115043"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647117085","data":{"timestamp":" 947647117084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647121734","data":{"timestamp":" 947647121733"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647123694","data":{"timestamp":" 947647123694"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647139469","data":{"timestamp":" 947647139469"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647141619","data":{"timestamp":" 947647141619"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647143129","data":{"timestamp":" 947647143129"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647144206","data":{"timestamp":" 947647144205"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" AKACHUKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647144212","data":{"timestamp":" 947647144212"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGAE"," userResponse":" KIGAE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647144718","data":{"timestamp":" 947647144718"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647149179","data":{"timestamp":" 947647149179"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647149184","data":{"timestamp":" 947647149183"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUNGU"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647153057","data":{"timestamp":" 947647153057"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647161995","data":{"timestamp":" 947647161995"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647163671","data":{"timestamp":" 947647163670"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647164458","data":{"timestamp":" 947647164457"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647168135","data":{"timestamp":" 947647168135"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647174252","data":{"timestamp":" 947647174252"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647174639","data":{"timestamp":" 947647174639"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647175549","data":{"timestamp":" 947647175549"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647177260","data":{"timestamp":" 947647177260"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647203821","data":{"timestamp":" 947647203821"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647207637","data":{"timestamp":" 947647207637"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647218252","data":{"timestamp":" 947647218252"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647219921","data":{"timestamp":" 947647219921"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647223361","data":{"timestamp":" 947647223361"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647224842","data":{"timestamp":" 947647224842"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647248308","data":{"timestamp":" 947647248308"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647258121","data":{"timestamp":" 947647258121"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647261933","data":{"timestamp":" 947647261933"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" USADIZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647263104","data":{"timestamp":" 947647263103"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647266739","data":{"timestamp":" 947647266739"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647272002","data":{"timestamp":" 947647272002"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647273648","data":{"timestamp":" 947647273648"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647275281","data":{"timestamp":" 947647275281"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647281522","data":{"timestamp":" 947647281522"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647281640","data":{"timestamp":" 947647281640"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647286560","data":{"timestamp":" 947647286560"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647288776","data":{"timestamp":" 947647288776"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647290978","data":{"timestamp":" 947647290978"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647292848","data":{"timestamp":" 947647292848"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647294021","data":{"timestamp":" 947647294021"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647297357","data":{"timestamp":" 947647297356"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" START_WAKIMCHUKULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647299467","data":{"timestamp":" 947647299467"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647305711","data":{"timestamp":" 947647305711"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647308087","data":{"timestamp":" 947647308087"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647309402","data":{"timestamp":" 947647309402"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647312615","data":{"timestamp":" 947647312615"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647315043","data":{"timestamp":" 947647315043"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647317601","data":{"timestamp":" 947647317601"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647321323","data":{"timestamp":" 947647321323"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647323384","data":{"timestamp":" 947647323384"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647324962","data":{"timestamp":" 947647324962"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647326382","data":{"timestamp":" 947647326382"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647328493","data":{"timestamp":" 947647328493"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647331821","data":{"timestamp":" 947647331820"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647334544","data":{"timestamp":" 947647334544"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647338089","data":{"timestamp":" 947647338089"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647338409","data":{"timestamp":" 947647338409"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647338413","data":{"timestamp":" 947647338413"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647339960","data":{"timestamp":" 947647339959"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647342238","data":{"timestamp":" 947647342238"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647343395","data":{"timestamp":" 947647343395"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647344969","data":{"timestamp":" 947647344969"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647346240","data":{"timestamp":" 947647346240"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647346942","data":{"timestamp":" 947647346942"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647348267","data":{"timestamp":" 947647348267"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647349371","data":{"timestamp":" 947647349371"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647351298","data":{"timestamp":" 947647351298"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647352364","data":{"timestamp":" 947647352364"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647353380","data":{"timestamp":" 947647353380"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647355262","data":{"timestamp":" 947647355261"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647356988","data":{"timestamp":" 947647356987"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647359771","data":{"timestamp":" 947647359771"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647362123","data":{"timestamp":" 947647362123"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647364178","data":{"timestamp":" 947647364177"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647364475","data":{"timestamp":" 947647364475"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647366786","data":{"timestamp":" 947647366786"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647368304","data":{"timestamp":" 947647368303"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647369280","data":{"timestamp":" 947647369280"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647371616","data":{"timestamp":" 947647371616"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647373008","data":{"timestamp":" 947647373007"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647375184","data":{"timestamp":" 947647375184"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647376823","data":{"timestamp":" 947647376822"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647378645","data":{"timestamp":" 947647378644"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647379432","data":{"timestamp":" 947647379432"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647380582","data":{"timestamp":" 947647380582"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647384188","data":{"timestamp":" 947647384188"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647388765","data":{"timestamp":" 947647388765"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647390496","data":{"timestamp":" 947647390496"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647391459","data":{"timestamp":" 947647391458"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647393343","data":{"timestamp":" 947647393343"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647395174","data":{"timestamp":" 947647395173"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647396859","data":{"timestamp":" 947647396859"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647399512","data":{"timestamp":" 947647399512"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" KUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647401824","data":{"timestamp":" 947647401824"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647403721","data":{"timestamp":" 947647403721"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647405176","data":{"timestamp":" 947647405175"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647407127","data":{"timestamp":" 947647407127"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647408760","data":{"timestamp":" 947647408760"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647410637","data":{"timestamp":" 947647410637"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647415269","data":{"timestamp":" 947647415269"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647417889","data":{"timestamp":" 947647417889"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647421555","data":{"timestamp":" 947647421554"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647426230","data":{"timestamp":" 947647426230"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647428262","data":{"timestamp":" 947647428262"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647430455","data":{"timestamp":" 947647430455"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647436805","data":{"timestamp":" 947647436805"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647437745","data":{"timestamp":" 947647437744"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647438643","data":{"timestamp":" 947647438643"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647441961","data":{"timestamp":" 947647441960"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" START_LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647443995","data":{"timestamp":" 947647443995"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647445422","data":{"timestamp":" 947647445422"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647446885","data":{"timestamp":" 947647446885"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647449108","data":{"timestamp":" 947647449108"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647449140","data":{"timestamp":" 947647449140"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647450633","data":{"timestamp":" 947647450633"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647453078","data":{"timestamp":" 947647453078"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647454543","data":{"timestamp":" 947647454543"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647455900","data":{"timestamp":" 947647455900"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647457050","data":{"timestamp":" 947647457050"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647461333","data":{"timestamp":" 947647461333"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" START_HALIKUTOSHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647462460","data":{"timestamp":" 947647462460"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" START_AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647464275","data":{"timestamp":" 947647464275"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647468427","data":{"timestamp":" 947647468427"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647469353","data":{"timestamp":" 947647469353"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647471566","data":{"timestamp":" 947647471566"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647473809","data":{"timestamp":" 947647473809"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647475815","data":{"timestamp":" 947647475815"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647477983","data":{"timestamp":" 947647477983"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647480050","data":{"timestamp":" 947647480050"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647480630","data":{"timestamp":" 947647480630"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647482471","data":{"timestamp":" 947647482471"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647482849","data":{"timestamp":" 947647482849"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647487855","data":{"timestamp":" 947647487854"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647490189","data":{"timestamp":" 947647490188"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647491930","data":{"timestamp":" 947647491930"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647493515","data":{"timestamp":" 947647493513"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647496584","data":{"timestamp":" 947647496584"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647498086","data":{"timestamp":" 947647498086"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647498249","data":{"timestamp":" 947647498249"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647503681","data":{"timestamp":" 947647503681"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647507514","data":{"timestamp":" 947647507514"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647509261","data":{"timestamp":" 947647509261"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647510863","data":{"timestamp":" 947647510863"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647512542","data":{"timestamp":" 947647512541"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647514030","data":{"timestamp":" 947647514029"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647518717","data":{"timestamp":" 947647518716"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647521114","data":{"timestamp":" 947647521114"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647522566","data":{"timestamp":" 947647522565"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647523645","data":{"timestamp":" 947647523645"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647529353","data":{"timestamp":" 947647529353"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647529357","data":{"timestamp":" 947647529357"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647530109","data":{"timestamp":" 947647530109"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647530117","data":{"timestamp":" 947647530117"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647531862","data":{"timestamp":" 947647531862"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647534061","data":{"timestamp":" 947647534061"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647537438","data":{"timestamp":" 947647537438"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647541157","data":{"timestamp":" 947647541157"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647542690","data":{"timestamp":" 947647542690"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647543385","data":{"timestamp":" 947647543385"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647545098","data":{"timestamp":" 947647545098"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647546303","data":{"timestamp":" 947647546303"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647546786","data":{"timestamp":" 947647546786"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647548335","data":{"timestamp":" 947647548334"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" UNARUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647549972","data":{"timestamp":" 947647549971"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647552981","data":{"timestamp":" 947647552981"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647554000","data":{"timestamp":" 947647554000"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" NIKIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647555181","data":{"timestamp":" 947647555181"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647557015","data":{"timestamp":" 947647557015"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647558727","data":{"timestamp":" 947647558726"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647561735","data":{"timestamp":" 947647561735"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647562542","data":{"timestamp":" 947647562542"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647562939","data":{"timestamp":" 947647562938"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647563301","data":{"timestamp":" 947647563300"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" LIMEZIMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647565269","data":{"timestamp":" 947647565269"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647569171","data":{"timestamp":" 947647569171"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647570758","data":{"timestamp":" 947647570757"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647574849","data":{"timestamp":" 947647574848"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647578879","data":{"timestamp":" 947647578879"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647580907","data":{"timestamp":" 947647580907"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647583635","data":{"timestamp":" 947647583635"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647583742","data":{"timestamp":" 947647583742"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647585715","data":{"timestamp":" 947647585715"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647589006","data":{"timestamp":" 947647589006"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647591495","data":{"timestamp":" 947647591495"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647593236","data":{"timestamp":" 947647593236"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647595050","data":{"timestamp":" 947647595050"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647597381","data":{"timestamp":" 947647597381"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647598797","data":{"timestamp":" 947647598797"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647606694","data":{"timestamp":" 947647606694"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647609663","data":{"timestamp":" 947647609663"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647611640","data":{"timestamp":" 947647611639"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647613116","data":{"timestamp":" 947647613116"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647614938","data":{"timestamp":" 947647614938"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647616409","data":{"timestamp":" 947647616409"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647624686","data":{"timestamp":" 947647624686"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647626291","data":{"timestamp":" 947647626291"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647627370","data":{"timestamp":" 947647627370"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647631968","data":{"timestamp":" 947647631968"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647633750","data":{"timestamp":" 947647633749"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647636623","data":{"timestamp":" 947647636623"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647647792","data":{"timestamp":" 947647647792"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647649260","data":{"timestamp":" 947647649259"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647655812","data":{"timestamp":" 947647655812"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647657046","data":{"timestamp":" 947647657046"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647658762","data":{"timestamp":" 947647658762"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647660612","data":{"timestamp":" 947647660612"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647661883","data":{"timestamp":" 947647661883"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647663303","data":{"timestamp":" 947647663303"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647664933","data":{"timestamp":" 947647664933"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647667419","data":{"timestamp":" 947647667419"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" ALIRUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647675006","data":{"timestamp":" 947647675006"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647676331","data":{"timestamp":" 947647676331"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647679004","data":{"timestamp":" 947647679004"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647680950","data":{"timestamp":" 947647680950"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647684609","data":{"timestamp":" 947647684609"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647689973","data":{"timestamp":" 947647689972"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEBA"," userResponse":" BEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647692777","data":{"timestamp":" 947647692777"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647702888","data":{"timestamp":" 947647702888"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647709478","data":{"timestamp":" 947647709478"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JINGINE"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647712691","data":{"timestamp":" 947647712691"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647718857","data":{"timestamp":" 947647718857"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647729238","data":{"timestamp":" 947647729238"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647731545","data":{"timestamp":" 947647731545"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647731812","data":{"timestamp":" 947647731811"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647733550","data":{"timestamp":" 947647733550"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647737513","data":{"timestamp":" 947647737513"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647741608","data":{"timestamp":" 947647741608"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647743068","data":{"timestamp":" 947647743068"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647749077","data":{"timestamp":" 947647749077"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647750636","data":{"timestamp":" 947647750636"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647752511","data":{"timestamp":" 947647752511"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647760086","data":{"timestamp":" 947647760086"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAENDA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647761538","data":{"timestamp":" 947647761538"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAENDA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647763270","data":{"timestamp":" 947647763269"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647764569","data":{"timestamp":" 947647764569"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647766727","data":{"timestamp":" 947647766726"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647768198","data":{"timestamp":" 947647768198"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647770031","data":{"timestamp":" 947647770031"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647773336","data":{"timestamp":" 947647773336"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" START_AKAFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647774782","data":{"timestamp":" 947647774781"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647775698","data":{"timestamp":" 947647775698"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647777935","data":{"timestamp":" 947647777934"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647779504","data":{"timestamp":" 947647779504"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647782808","data":{"timestamp":" 947647782808"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647784536","data":{"timestamp":" 947647784536"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647786430","data":{"timestamp":" 947647786430"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" START_KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647788246","data":{"timestamp":" 947647788246"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647789978","data":{"timestamp":" 947647789978"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647792154","data":{"timestamp":" 947647792154"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647794681","data":{"timestamp":" 947647794681"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647798739","data":{"timestamp":" 947647798738"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647800949","data":{"timestamp":" 947647800948"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647805642","data":{"timestamp":" 947647805642"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647806627","data":{"timestamp":" 947647806627"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647807900","data":{"timestamp":" 947647807900"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647812120","data":{"timestamp":" 947647812120"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647813073","data":{"timestamp":" 947647813073"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647816248","data":{"timestamp":" 947647816248"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHANGIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647821593","data":{"timestamp":" 947647821593"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" START_AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647823623","data":{"timestamp":" 947647823622"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647824584","data":{"timestamp":" 947647824583"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647825802","data":{"timestamp":" 947647825802"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647827406","data":{"timestamp":" 947647827405"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647831794","data":{"timestamp":" 947647831794"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647836194","data":{"timestamp":" 947647836194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647839851","data":{"timestamp":" 947647839851"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647841593","data":{"timestamp":" 947647841593"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647844682","data":{"timestamp":" 947647844682"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647848734","data":{"timestamp":" 947647848733"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647850193","data":{"timestamp":" 947647850193"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647852595","data":{"timestamp":" 947647852594"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647853952","data":{"timestamp":" 947647853952"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647855574","data":{"timestamp":" 947647855574"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647859272","data":{"timestamp":" 947647859272"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647860211","data":{"timestamp":" 947647860211"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" AKARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647863580","data":{"timestamp":" 947647863580"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647863724","data":{"timestamp":" 947647863724"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647866497","data":{"timestamp":" 947647866497"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647868015","data":{"timestamp":" 947647868015"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647868969","data":{"timestamp":" 947647868968"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647871291","data":{"timestamp":" 947647871291"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647872879","data":{"timestamp":" 947647872879"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647875962","data":{"timestamp":" 947647875962"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647877787","data":{"timestamp":" 947647877787"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647879633","data":{"timestamp":" 947647879633"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647884182","data":{"timestamp":" 947647884182"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647885836","data":{"timestamp":" 947647885835"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647887439","data":{"timestamp":" 947647887439"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647887444","data":{"timestamp":" 947647887444"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647891960","data":{"timestamp":" 947647891960"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647894520","data":{"timestamp":" 947647894520"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647896621","data":{"timestamp":" 947647896620"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647898344","data":{"timestamp":" 947647898344"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647903699","data":{"timestamp":" 947647903699"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647905669","data":{"timestamp":" 947647905669"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647907206","data":{"timestamp":" 947647907206"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647909067","data":{"timestamp":" 947647909067"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647917017","data":{"timestamp":" 947647917017"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647917606","data":{"timestamp":" 947647917606"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647920057","data":{"timestamp":" 947647920057"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647922112","data":{"timestamp":" 947647922112"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647922885","data":{"timestamp":" 947647922885"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" START_MATAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647926148","data":{"timestamp":" 947647926148"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647927532","data":{"timestamp":" 947647927532"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647928440","data":{"timestamp":" 947647928440"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647946782","data":{"timestamp":" 947647946782"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647946786","data":{"timestamp":" 947647946786"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647948412","data":{"timestamp":" 947647948412"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647953703","data":{"timestamp":" 947647953702"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647954990","data":{"timestamp":" 947647954989"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647955284","data":{"timestamp":" 947647955284"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647967349","data":{"timestamp":" 947647967349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" KUCHUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647969069","data":{"timestamp":" 947647969067"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647969984","data":{"timestamp":" 947647969984"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647974292","data":{"timestamp":" 947647974292"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647975884","data":{"timestamp":" 947647975881"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647985473","data":{"timestamp":" 947647985473"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647987100","data":{"timestamp":" 947647987100"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647989334","data":{"timestamp":" 947647989333"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647991839","data":{"timestamp":" 947647991839"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUMA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647993078","data":{"timestamp":" 947647993077"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUMA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647994548","data":{"timestamp":" 947647994548"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647996616","data":{"timestamp":" 947647996616"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648003132","data":{"timestamp":" 947648003132"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648004701","data":{"timestamp":" 947648004701"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648005851","data":{"timestamp":" 947648005851"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648014860","data":{"timestamp":" 947648014860"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648016457","data":{"timestamp":" 947648016457"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648017620","data":{"timestamp":" 947648017620"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648019738","data":{"timestamp":" 947648019738"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648021508","data":{"timestamp":" 947648021507"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648022588","data":{"timestamp":" 947648022588"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648028497","data":{"timestamp":" 947648028497"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648029256","data":{"timestamp":" 947648029256"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648030525","data":{"timestamp":" 947648030525"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648031957","data":{"timestamp":" 947648031957"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648034459","data":{"timestamp":" 947648034459"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648035250","data":{"timestamp":" 947648035250"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648036040","data":{"timestamp":" 947648036040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" START_LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648037065","data":{"timestamp":" 947648037065"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648037908","data":{"timestamp":" 947648037907"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648039932","data":{"timestamp":" 947648039932"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIONA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648041457","data":{"timestamp":" 947648041457"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIONA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648043331","data":{"timestamp":" 947648043331"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648044489","data":{"timestamp":" 947648044489"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648046997","data":{"timestamp":" 947648046997"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648048271","data":{"timestamp":" 947648048271"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648053373","data":{"timestamp":" 947648053373"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648055069","data":{"timestamp":" 947648055069"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648057331","data":{"timestamp":" 947648057330"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648059356","data":{"timestamp":" 947648059355"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648060661","data":{"timestamp":" 947648060661"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648060664","data":{"timestamp":" 947648060664"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648064650","data":{"timestamp":" 947648064650"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648066194","data":{"timestamp":" 947648066194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648067620","data":{"timestamp":" 947648067619"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648072800","data":{"timestamp":" 947648072800"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWEKA"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648076452","data":{"timestamp":" 947648076452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWEKA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648078084","data":{"timestamp":" 947648078084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648079880","data":{"timestamp":" 947648079880"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" ALICHUKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648080803","data":{"timestamp":" 947648080803"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648082446","data":{"timestamp":" 947648082446"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648083426","data":{"timestamp":" 947648083426"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648084619","data":{"timestamp":" 947648084618"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648084622","data":{"timestamp":" 947648084622"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648085139","data":{"timestamp":" 947648085139"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648088726","data":{"timestamp":" 947648088725"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648089705","data":{"timestamp":" 947648089705"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648091488","data":{"timestamp":" 947648091488"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648092901","data":{"timestamp":" 947648092901"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648105039","data":{"timestamp":" 947648105039"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" ALICHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648106376","data":{"timestamp":" 947648106376"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648111454","data":{"timestamp":" 947648111454"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648113218","data":{"timestamp":" 947648113218"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648115614","data":{"timestamp":" 947648115614"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648119313","data":{"timestamp":" 947648119313"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648123634","data":{"timestamp":" 947648123634"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648126254","data":{"timestamp":" 947648126254"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648129963","data":{"timestamp":" 947648129963"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648131536","data":{"timestamp":" 947648131536"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648134214","data":{"timestamp":" 947648134214"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUPATA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648136611","data":{"timestamp":" 947648136611"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUPATA"," userResponse":" START_HAWAKUPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648138554","data":{"timestamp":" 947648138553"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648141255","data":{"timestamp":" 947648141255"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648144279","data":{"timestamp":" 947648144278"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648146022","data":{"timestamp":" 947648146021"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648156895","data":{"timestamp":" 947648156895"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648159126","data":{"timestamp":" 947648159126"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648160049","data":{"timestamp":" 947648160049"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648160746","data":{"timestamp":" 947648160746"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648160750","data":{"timestamp":" 947648160750"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648167765","data":{"timestamp":" 947648167765"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAANZA"," userResponse":" START_LIKAANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648169496","data":{"timestamp":" 947648169496"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAANZA"," userResponse":" KUTANDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648171184","data":{"timestamp":" 947648171184"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648172064","data":{"timestamp":" 947648172064"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTANDA"," userResponse":" KUTANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648175372","data":{"timestamp":" 947648175372"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648178195","data":{"timestamp":" 947648178194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648179897","data":{"timestamp":" 947648179896"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648180692","data":{"timestamp":" 947648180692"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648182424","data":{"timestamp":" 947648182424"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648183953","data":{"timestamp":" 947648183953"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648184107","data":{"timestamp":" 947648184107"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648186006","data":{"timestamp":" 947648186006"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648188742","data":{"timestamp":" 947648188742"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648189671","data":{"timestamp":" 947648189671"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648193094","data":{"timestamp":" 947648193094"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648194694","data":{"timestamp":" 947648194693"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648195986","data":{"timestamp":" 947648195986"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648198953","data":{"timestamp":" 947648198953"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648200435","data":{"timestamp":" 947648200434"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648207643","data":{"timestamp":" 947648207642"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648208632","data":{"timestamp":" 947648208632"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648211321","data":{"timestamp":" 947648211321"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIAMBIA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648213377","data":{"timestamp":" 947648213377"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIAMBIA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648215330","data":{"timestamp":" 947648215330"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648219087","data":{"timestamp":" 947648219087"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648219185","data":{"timestamp":" 947648219185"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648221231","data":{"timestamp":" 947648221231"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648223035","data":{"timestamp":" 947648223035"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648223922","data":{"timestamp":" 947648223922"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIRUKE"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648226307","data":{"timestamp":" 947648226307"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIRUKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648228360","data":{"timestamp":" 947648228360"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HEWANI"," userResponse":" LIKAANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648230026","data":{"timestamp":" 947648230025"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HEWANI"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648231572","data":{"timestamp":" 947648231572"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648232039","data":{"timestamp":" 947648232039"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648232830","data":{"timestamp":" 947648232830"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648236470","data":{"timestamp":" 947648236470"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648237951","data":{"timestamp":" 947648237951"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHUSHA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648241059","data":{"timestamp":" 947648241059"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHUSHA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648242878","data":{"timestamp":" 947648242878"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHUSHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648243152","data":{"timestamp":" 947648243152"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PUMZI"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648245186","data":{"timestamp":" 947648245185"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUMZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648245830","data":{"timestamp":" 947648245830"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648249349","data":{"timestamp":" 947648249349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648252893","data":{"timestamp":" 947648252893"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648260454","data":{"timestamp":" 947648260454"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648262270","data":{"timestamp":" 947648262270"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" AKAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648262576","data":{"timestamp":" 947648262576"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648263000","data":{"timestamp":" 947648263000"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648264440","data":{"timestamp":" 947648264440"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648265638","data":{"timestamp":" 947648265638"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648267264","data":{"timestamp":" 947648267264"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648268356","data":{"timestamp":" 947648268356"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648269814","data":{"timestamp":" 947648269814"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648271816","data":{"timestamp":" 947648271816"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" START_HATARI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648273557","data":{"timestamp":" 947648273557"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648274892","data":{"timestamp":" 947648274891"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648277170","data":{"timestamp":" 947648277170"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648278233","data":{"timestamp":" 947648278233"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648278879","data":{"timestamp":" 947648278879"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648281311","data":{"timestamp":" 947648281311"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648282815","data":{"timestamp":" 947648282814"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNA"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648283567","data":{"timestamp":" 947648283567"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648284484","data":{"timestamp":" 947648284484"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMU"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648287199","data":{"timestamp":" 947648287199"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648289606","data":{"timestamp":" 947648289606"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYORORO"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648297042","data":{"timestamp":" 947648297042"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYORORO"," userResponse":" NYORORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648302025","data":{"timestamp":" 947648302025"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648309253","data":{"timestamp":" 947648309253"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648311447","data":{"timestamp":" 947648311447"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648312661","data":{"timestamp":" 947648312661"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648314428","data":{"timestamp":" 947648314427"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648316829","data":{"timestamp":" 947648316828"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUANZE"," userResponse":" TUANZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648316832","data":{"timestamp":" 947648316832"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648317450","data":{"timestamp":" 947648317450"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MM"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648320025","data":{"timestamp":" 947648320025"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648322454","data":{"timestamp":" 947648322454"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648323881","data":{"timestamp":" 947648323881"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSINIUE"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648326931","data":{"timestamp":" 947648326931"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MSINIUE"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648328728","data":{"timestamp":" 947648328727"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSINIUE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648329006","data":{"timestamp":" 947648329006"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648333245","data":{"timestamp":" 947648333245"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648334911","data":{"timestamp":" 947648334911"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648336707","data":{"timestamp":" 947648336707"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648341131","data":{"timestamp":" 947648341131"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648342946","data":{"timestamp":" 947648342945"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648344134","data":{"timestamp":" 947648344133"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648348068","data":{"timestamp":" 947648348068"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648349588","data":{"timestamp":" 947648349587"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648349888","data":{"timestamp":" 947648349888"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648351606","data":{"timestamp":" 947648351605"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648353392","data":{"timestamp":" 947648353392"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648354542","data":{"timestamp":" 947648354542"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648358162","data":{"timestamp":" 947648358162"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648360602","data":{"timestamp":" 947648360602"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" WENU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648363431","data":{"timestamp":" 947648363431"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" WENU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648364933","data":{"timestamp":" 947648364933"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648366528","data":{"timestamp":" 947648366528"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAMJUI"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648369295","data":{"timestamp":" 947648369295"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAMJUI"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648371024","data":{"timestamp":" 947648371024"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMJUI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648371600","data":{"timestamp":" 947648371600"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648373368","data":{"timestamp":" 947648373368"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648374980","data":{"timestamp":" 947648374980"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648376579","data":{"timestamp":" 947648376579"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648377535","data":{"timestamp":" 947648377535"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648377909","data":{"timestamp":" 947648377908"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648378227","data":{"timestamp":" 947648378227"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENU"," userResponse":" WENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648380506","data":{"timestamp":" 947648380506"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOTEA"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648381590","data":{"timestamp":" 947648381590"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOTEA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648383489","data":{"timestamp":" 947648383489"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOTEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648384465","data":{"timestamp":" 947648384465"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648385611","data":{"timestamp":" 947648385611"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648387253","data":{"timestamp":" 947648387253"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648387416","data":{"timestamp":" 947648387416"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648388401","data":{"timestamp":" 947648388401"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" NYORORO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648390357","data":{"timestamp":" 947648390357"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" HAMJUI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648391899","data":{"timestamp":" 947648391899"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648392446","data":{"timestamp":" 947648392446"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZENU"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648393892","data":{"timestamp":" 947648393892"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZENU"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648395206","data":{"timestamp":" 947648395206"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZENU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648395910","data":{"timestamp":" 947648395910"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648396758","data":{"timestamp":" 947648396758"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648398143","data":{"timestamp":" 947648398142"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648400219","data":{"timestamp":" 947648400219"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" ALIYEWEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648401271","data":{"timestamp":" 947648401270"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648403098","data":{"timestamp":" 947648403098"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648403406","data":{"timestamp":" 947648403406"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648405082","data":{"timestamp":" 947648405082"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648407045","data":{"timestamp":" 947648407045"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648408645","data":{"timestamp":" 947648408645"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPATA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648410003","data":{"timestamp":" 947648410002"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPATA"," userResponse":" KUNIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648412239","data":{"timestamp":" 947648412238"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648413037","data":{"timestamp":" 947648413037"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648414692","data":{"timestamp":" 947648414691"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648417788","data":{"timestamp":" 947648417788"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYINYI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648421925","data":{"timestamp":" 947648421925"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYINYI"," userResponse":" ZENU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648423421","data":{"timestamp":" 947648423421"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINYI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648423700","data":{"timestamp":" 947648423700"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648426199","data":{"timestamp":" 947648426199"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648426202","data":{"timestamp":" 947648426202"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648429600","data":{"timestamp":" 947648429600"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648432342","data":{"timestamp":" 947648432342"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648434407","data":{"timestamp":" 947648434407"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648436982","data":{"timestamp":" 947648436982"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648440774","data":{"timestamp":" 947648440774"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648442381","data":{"timestamp":" 947648442381"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648443547","data":{"timestamp":" 947648443547"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648445318","data":{"timestamp":" 947648445318"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648446399","data":{"timestamp":" 947648446399"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648451734","data":{"timestamp":" 947648451734"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" START_WAKAMWONEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648454011","data":{"timestamp":" 947648454010"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" WENU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648455725","data":{"timestamp":" 947648455725"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648460598","data":{"timestamp":" 947648460598"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648463326","data":{"timestamp":" 947648463326"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648463938","data":{"timestamp":" 947648463938"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648464918","data":{"timestamp":" 947648464918"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648465886","data":{"timestamp":" 947648465886"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648467491","data":{"timestamp":" 947648467491"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUAMINI"," userResponse":" START_HAKUAMINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648469620","data":{"timestamp":" 947648469620"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUAMINI"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648472625","data":{"timestamp":" 947648472625"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUAMINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648477587","data":{"timestamp":" 947648477586"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAJUA"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648480449","data":{"timestamp":" 947648480449"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAJUA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648482027","data":{"timestamp":" 947648482027"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAJUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648485679","data":{"timestamp":" 947648485679"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648485685","data":{"timestamp":" 947648485685"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648485692","data":{"timestamp":" 947648485691"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648487120","data":{"timestamp":" 947648487120"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648488102","data":{"timestamp":" 947648488102"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648489795","data":{"timestamp":" 947648489795"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648493277","data":{"timestamp":" 947648493277"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648495753","data":{"timestamp":" 947648495753"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648498260","data":{"timestamp":" 947648498260"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEZA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648499236","data":{"timestamp":" 947648499236"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEZA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648500977","data":{"timestamp":" 947648500977"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648502132","data":{"timestamp":" 947648502132"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648502842","data":{"timestamp":" 947648502841"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648504860","data":{"timestamp":" 947648504860"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUPU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648509612","data":{"timestamp":" 947648509612"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SUPU"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648511133","data":{"timestamp":" 947648511132"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUPU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648512212","data":{"timestamp":" 947648512212"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648512220","data":{"timestamp":" 947648512220"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATOPE"," userResponse":" MATOPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648512227","data":{"timestamp":" 947648512226"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648514719","data":{"timestamp":" 947648514719"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648516177","data":{"timestamp":" 947648516177"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648517770","data":{"timestamp":" 947648517769"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648519812","data":{"timestamp":" 947648519812"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMPATIA"," userResponse":" START_WALIMPATIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648521739","data":{"timestamp":" 947648521739"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMPATIA"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648523592","data":{"timestamp":" 947648523591"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMPATIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648524141","data":{"timestamp":" 947648524141"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648526019","data":{"timestamp":" 947648526019"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" HAKUAMINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648527520","data":{"timestamp":" 947648527520"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648528770","data":{"timestamp":" 947648528770"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648532390","data":{"timestamp":" 947648532390"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648535411","data":{"timestamp":" 947648535411"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648536734","data":{"timestamp":" 947648536733"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MACHAFU"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648539507","data":{"timestamp":" 947648539507"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimpatia kibuyu cha maji machafu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHAFU"," userResponse":" MACHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648540782","data":{"timestamp":" 947648540782"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYANGU"," userResponse":" NYANYANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648541557","data":{"timestamp":" 947648541557"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648544670","data":{"timestamp":" 947648544670"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648546402","data":{"timestamp":" 947648546402"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648550083","data":{"timestamp":" 947648550083"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKITENGEZA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648553783","data":{"timestamp":" 947648553783"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKITENGEZA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648555884","data":{"timestamp":" 947648555884"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITENGEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648556173","data":{"timestamp":" 947648556173"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUPU"," userResponse":" MATOPE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648557704","data":{"timestamp":" 947648557704"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUPU"," userResponse":" SUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648561538","data":{"timestamp":" 947648561538"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648567036","data":{"timestamp":" 947648567036"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648568089","data":{"timestamp":" 947648568089"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648571982","data":{"timestamp":" 947648571982"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648573364","data":{"timestamp":" 947648573364"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648575044","data":{"timestamp":" 947648575043"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648579751","data":{"timestamp":" 947648579750"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648581046","data":{"timestamp":" 947648581046"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648582785","data":{"timestamp":" 947648582785"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyanyangu alikuwa akitengeza supu kama hii Anansi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648584107","data":{"timestamp":" 947648584106"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648586058","data":{"timestamp":" 947648586058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648590510","data":{"timestamp":" 947648590509"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHIMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648592767","data":{"timestamp":" 947648592767"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHIMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648594521","data":{"timestamp":" 947648594521"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648596514","data":{"timestamp":" 947648596514"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" SHIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648597901","data":{"timestamp":" 947648597901"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648598989","data":{"timestamp":" 947648598989"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648599966","data":{"timestamp":" 947648599966"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648602652","data":{"timestamp":" 947648602651"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" MATOPE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648604100","data":{"timestamp":" 947648604100"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648605717","data":{"timestamp":" 947648605717"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKITUMIA"," userResponse":" HAKUAMINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648607770","data":{"timestamp":" 947648607770"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKITUMIA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648609491","data":{"timestamp":" 947648609490"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITUMIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648613569","data":{"timestamp":" 947648613569"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648615966","data":{"timestamp":" 947648615966"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648617153","data":{"timestamp":" 947648617153"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648618962","data":{"timestamp":" 947648618962"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648620303","data":{"timestamp":" 947648620303"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648624777","data":{"timestamp":" 947648624777"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648625703","data":{"timestamp":" 947648625702"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648626415","data":{"timestamp":" 947648626415"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648627434","data":{"timestamp":" 947648627434"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648629550","data":{"timestamp":" 947648629550"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOBOA"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648630883","data":{"timestamp":" 947648630883"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOBOA"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648632886","data":{"timestamp":" 947648632886"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOBOA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648639777","data":{"timestamp":" 947648639777"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648641695","data":{"timestamp":" 947648641695"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" MATOPE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648643309","data":{"timestamp":" 947648643308"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648644688","data":{"timestamp":" 947648644687"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648647816","data":{"timestamp":" 947648647815"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AKATOBOA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648649268","data":{"timestamp":" 947648649268"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648652954","data":{"timestamp":" 947648652954"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" MACHAFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648656567","data":{"timestamp":" 947648656567"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648658132","data":{"timestamp":" 947648658132"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648660192","data":{"timestamp":" 947648660192"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648661026","data":{"timestamp":" 947648661026"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648662730","data":{"timestamp":" 947648662730"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" START_HAKUAMINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648667317","data":{"timestamp":" 947648667316"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648668786","data":{"timestamp":" 947648668786"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648670665","data":{"timestamp":" 947648670665"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648674194","data":{"timestamp":" 947648674194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648675876","data":{"timestamp":" 947648675876"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648678426","data":{"timestamp":" 947648678426"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alichimba shimo kwenye ardhi akitumia mguu wake wa nyuma kisha akatoboa shimo kwenye kibuyu kwa mguu wake wa mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648679914","data":{"timestamp":" 947648679914"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" SHIMO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648682661","data":{"timestamp":" 947648682661"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648684520","data":{"timestamp":" 947648684520"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648685898","data":{"timestamp":" 947648685898"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648688730","data":{"timestamp":" 947648688730"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648689611","data":{"timestamp":" 947648689611"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648693545","data":{"timestamp":" 947648693545"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKINYWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648696078","data":{"timestamp":" 947648696078"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINYWA"," userResponse":" AKINYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648696572","data":{"timestamp":" 947648696572"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648696892","data":{"timestamp":" 947648696891"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648699619","data":{"timestamp":" 947648699619"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648702953","data":{"timestamp":" 947648702953"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648703549","data":{"timestamp":" 947648703549"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBE"," userResponse":" KUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648707534","data":{"timestamp":" 947648707533"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648709511","data":{"timestamp":" 947648709511"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKIMWAGIKA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648712084","data":{"timestamp":" 947648712084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YAKIMWAGIKA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648713888","data":{"timestamp":" 947648713888"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKIMWAGIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648715278","data":{"timestamp":" 947648715278"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITIA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648717024","data":{"timestamp":" 947648717024"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITIA"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648718500","data":{"timestamp":" 947648718499"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648719687","data":{"timestamp":" 947648719687"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648721210","data":{"timestamp":" 947648721210"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648723101","data":{"timestamp":" 947648723101"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" SUPU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648727090","data":{"timestamp":" 947648727090"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" START_YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648728428","data":{"timestamp":" 947648728427"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648730055","data":{"timestamp":" 947648730055"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648732761","data":{"timestamp":" 947648732761"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648734697","data":{"timestamp":" 947648734697"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijifanya kwamba alikuwa akinywa yale maji na kumbe yalikuwa yakimwagika kupitia katikati ya miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648738157","data":{"timestamp":" 947648738157"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAMU"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648739637","data":{"timestamp":" 947648739637"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMU"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648744615","data":{"timestamp":" 947648744614"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TUTAJUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648746277","data":{"timestamp":" 947648746277"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648750136","data":{"timestamp":" 947648750136"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648751946","data":{"timestamp":" 947648751945"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648751955","data":{"timestamp":" 947648751955"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648753575","data":{"timestamp":" 947648753575"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUDISHA"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648755778","data":{"timestamp":" 947648755778"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUDISHA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648757725","data":{"timestamp":" 947648757725"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUDISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648757909","data":{"timestamp":" 947648757909"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648766265","data":{"timestamp":" 947648766264"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648767818","data":{"timestamp":" 947648767818"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema huku akirudisha kibuyu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648769631","data":{"timestamp":" 947648769630"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648772559","data":{"timestamp":" 947648772559"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" START_SASA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648774242","data":{"timestamp":" 947648774242"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648776417","data":{"timestamp":" 947648776417"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMEJUA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648777713","data":{"timestamp":" 947648777713"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMEJUA"," userResponse":" TUMEJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648777822","data":{"timestamp":" 947648777822"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648778809","data":{"timestamp":" 947648778809"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648780072","data":{"timestamp":" 947648780072"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648780844","data":{"timestamp":" 947648780843"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648782974","data":{"timestamp":" 947648782974"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648784452","data":{"timestamp":" 947648784452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648784764","data":{"timestamp":" 947648784764"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648786882","data":{"timestamp":" 947648786882"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648788535","data":{"timestamp":" 947648788535"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648789189","data":{"timestamp":" 947648789189"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648791378","data":{"timestamp":" 947648791378"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648797033","data":{"timestamp":" 947648797032"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648799048","data":{"timestamp":" 947648799048"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648800404","data":{"timestamp":" 947648800404"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648802006","data":{"timestamp":" 947648802005"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648803133","data":{"timestamp":" 947648803133"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648820834","data":{"timestamp":" 947648820833"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648822299","data":{"timestamp":" 947648822299"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" START_WAKAMWAMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648824186","data":{"timestamp":" 947648824185"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa tumejua wewe bila shaka ni mmoja wetu  mamba wakamwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648825128","data":{"timestamp":" 947648825128"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648828980","data":{"timestamp":" 947648828980"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" START_TUMEJUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648831518","data":{"timestamp":" 947648831518"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648834503","data":{"timestamp":" 947648834503"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMRUHUSU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648837863","data":{"timestamp":" 947648837863"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648838326","data":{"timestamp":" 947648838326"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648840773","data":{"timestamp":" 947648840773"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648844586","data":{"timestamp":" 947648844586"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648845565","data":{"timestamp":" 947648845565"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648847302","data":{"timestamp":" 947648847301"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648849173","data":{"timestamp":" 947648849173"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648850123","data":{"timestamp":" 947648850123"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648850500","data":{"timestamp":" 947648850500"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648850504","data":{"timestamp":" 947648850503"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo walimruhusu Anansi kulala pamoja nao usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648855406","data":{"timestamp":" 947648855405"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648857354","data":{"timestamp":" 947648857354"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648859362","data":{"timestamp":" 947648859362"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648861462","data":{"timestamp":" 947648861462"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648863354","data":{"timestamp":" 947648863353"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648865874","data":{"timestamp":" 947648865874"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648871040","data":{"timestamp":" 947648871040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" START_NITAWAAMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648872890","data":{"timestamp":" 947648872889"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648873592","data":{"timestamp":" 947648873592"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648874843","data":{"timestamp":" 947648874843"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648876820","data":{"timestamp":" 947648876819"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648876988","data":{"timestamp":" 947648876988"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648878137","data":{"timestamp":" 947648878137"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648879713","data":{"timestamp":" 947648879712"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648884555","data":{"timestamp":" 947648884555"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648886156","data":{"timestamp":" 947648886155"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648888549","data":{"timestamp":" 947648888549"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648890429","data":{"timestamp":" 947648890429"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648891905","data":{"timestamp":" 947648891901"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648895918","data":{"timestamp":" 947648895918"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648896798","data":{"timestamp":" 947648896798"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" START_ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648898481","data":{"timestamp":" 947648898481"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648900489","data":{"timestamp":" 947648900488"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" START_KUHUSU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648902645","data":{"timestamp":" 947648902645"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648904534","data":{"timestamp":" 947648904534"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648904810","data":{"timestamp":" 947648904810"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648908762","data":{"timestamp":" 947648908762"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648910622","data":{"timestamp":" 947648910622"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648912497","data":{"timestamp":" 947648912497"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANZA"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648915745","data":{"timestamp":" 947648915745"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANZA"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648917384","data":{"timestamp":" 947648917383"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648918308","data":{"timestamp":" 947648918308"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648925036","data":{"timestamp":" 947648925036"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648926602","data":{"timestamp":" 947648926601"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho asubuhi nitawaambia hadithi kuhusu maisha yangu Anansi aliwaambia walipokuwa wakianza kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648929827","data":{"timestamp":" 947648929827"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648934021","data":{"timestamp":" 947648934020"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648934880","data":{"timestamp":" 947648934880"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" START_ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648937084","data":{"timestamp":" 947648937083"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648942247","data":{"timestamp":" 947648942247"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648944102","data":{"timestamp":" 947648944102"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648945911","data":{"timestamp":" 947648945910"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMAKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648947717","data":{"timestamp":" 947648947717"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMAKA"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648949570","data":{"timestamp":" 947648949570"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648951736","data":{"timestamp":" 947648951736"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648953449","data":{"timestamp":" 947648953448"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" START_ASUBUHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648955330","data":{"timestamp":" 947648955330"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648957706","data":{"timestamp":" 947648957706"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648960208","data":{"timestamp":" 947648960208"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648965136","data":{"timestamp":" 947648965136"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648965143","data":{"timestamp":" 947648965143"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWAMSHA"," userResponse":" AKAMWAMSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648966264","data":{"timestamp":" 947648966264"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648967608","data":{"timestamp":" 947648967608"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648970027","data":{"timestamp":" 947648970027"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648971760","data":{"timestamp":" 947648971760"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648973471","data":{"timestamp":" 947648973471"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Anansi alimaka asubuhi na mapema akamwamsha mamba mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648975319","data":{"timestamp":" 947648975319"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIMAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648978842","data":{"timestamp":" 947648978842"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648980544","data":{"timestamp":" 947648980544"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648982528","data":{"timestamp":" 947648982528"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648983890","data":{"timestamp":" 947648983889"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648985411","data":{"timestamp":" 947648985410"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648986093","data":{"timestamp":" 947648986093"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIMLETE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648989626","data":{"timestamp":" 947648989626"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NIMLETE"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648991256","data":{"timestamp":" 947648991255"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMLETE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648991551","data":{"timestamp":" 947648991551"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648992478","data":{"timestamp":" 947648992478"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648993253","data":{"timestamp":" 947648993252"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648993635","data":{"timestamp":" 947648993634"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648995961","data":{"timestamp":" 947648995961"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648998302","data":{"timestamp":" 947648998302"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648999581","data":{"timestamp":" 947648999581"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649002921","data":{"timestamp":" 947649002920"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649004918","data":{"timestamp":" 947649004918"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUHADITHIA"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649012187","data":{"timestamp":" 947649012186"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUHADITHIA"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649014164","data":{"timestamp":" 947649014163"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kwenda nimlete mke na watoto wangu ili wanisaidie kuhadithia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHADITHIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649017137","data":{"timestamp":" 947649017136"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649018333","data":{"timestamp":" 947649018333"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649019553","data":{"timestamp":" 947649019553"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649021528","data":{"timestamp":" 947649021528"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UTANISAIDIA"," userResponse":" NIMLETE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649023214","data":{"timestamp":" 947649023214"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UTANISAIDIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649025097","data":{"timestamp":" 947649025097"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANISAIDIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649025753","data":{"timestamp":" 947649025753"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649026712","data":{"timestamp":" 947649026712"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" NIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649027482","data":{"timestamp":" 947649027481"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETA"," userResponse":" NIENDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649029614","data":{"timestamp":" 947649029614"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETA"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649031288","data":{"timestamp":" 947649031287"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649034638","data":{"timestamp":" 947649034638"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649041848","data":{"timestamp":" 947649041848"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649041852","data":{"timestamp":" 947649041852"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649041856","data":{"timestamp":" 947649041856"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649044799","data":{"timestamp":" 947649044799"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" f147b6b4-a12a-4833-9f84-3f28609d976a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je utanisaidia niende kuwaleta kabla ya wengine kuamka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732697853","data":{"timestamp":" 947732697853"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732699561","data":{"timestamp":" 947732699561"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732704724","data":{"timestamp":" 947732704724"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732706572","data":{"timestamp":" 947732706572"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732708567","data":{"timestamp":" 947732708567"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732709916","data":{"timestamp":" 947732709916"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732710086","data":{"timestamp":" 947732710086"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732711323","data":{"timestamp":" 947732711323"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732711811","data":{"timestamp":" 947732711811"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732714841","data":{"timestamp":" 947732714840"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732714849","data":{"timestamp":" 947732714849"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732715886","data":{"timestamp":" 947732715886"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732716851","data":{"timestamp":" 947732716851"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732718080","data":{"timestamp":" 947732718080"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732720002","data":{"timestamp":" 947732720001"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732723623","data":{"timestamp":" 947732723623"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732724852","data":{"timestamp":" 947732724852"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732726286","data":{"timestamp":" 947732726283"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732734484","data":{"timestamp":" 947732734483"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" START_KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732735639","data":{"timestamp":" 947732735639"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732737381","data":{"timestamp":" 947732737380"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732738866","data":{"timestamp":" 947732738866"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732740117","data":{"timestamp":" 947732740117"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732741991","data":{"timestamp":" 947732741991"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732743983","data":{"timestamp":" 947732743983"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732745284","data":{"timestamp":" 947732745284"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732746220","data":{"timestamp":" 947732746220"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732747729","data":{"timestamp":" 947732747728"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732748709","data":{"timestamp":" 947732748709"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732750496","data":{"timestamp":" 947732750496"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732752339","data":{"timestamp":" 947732752338"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732752907","data":{"timestamp":" 947732752907"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732754079","data":{"timestamp":" 947732754079"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732755173","data":{"timestamp":" 947732755173"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732755761","data":{"timestamp":" 947732755761"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732760358","data":{"timestamp":" 947732760357"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732762087","data":{"timestamp":" 947732762086"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732763947","data":{"timestamp":" 947732763947"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732765944","data":{"timestamp":" 947732765943"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732769355","data":{"timestamp":" 947732769355"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732769359","data":{"timestamp":" 947732769359"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732769993","data":{"timestamp":" 947732769993"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732770465","data":{"timestamp":" 947732770465"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732773203","data":{"timestamp":" 947732773203"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732774568","data":{"timestamp":" 947732774568"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732776145","data":{"timestamp":" 947732776144"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732776641","data":{"timestamp":" 947732776641"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732777861","data":{"timestamp":" 947732777861"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732779666","data":{"timestamp":" 947732779666"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732781279","data":{"timestamp":" 947732781278"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732782824","data":{"timestamp":" 947732782823"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732784453","data":{"timestamp":" 947732784453"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732785358","data":{"timestamp":" 947732785358"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732785362","data":{"timestamp":" 947732785362"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732787972","data":{"timestamp":" 947732787972"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732794767","data":{"timestamp":" 947732794767"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732796291","data":{"timestamp":" 947732796291"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732796946","data":{"timestamp":" 947732796946"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732797856","data":{"timestamp":" 947732797855"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" START_WALIRUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732799472","data":{"timestamp":" 947732799472"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732801736","data":{"timestamp":" 947732801736"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732803235","data":{"timestamp":" 947732803235"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732804502","data":{"timestamp":" 947732804502"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732804797","data":{"timestamp":" 947732804797"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732807484","data":{"timestamp":" 947732807484"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732809143","data":{"timestamp":" 947732809142"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732810514","data":{"timestamp":" 947732810513"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732813163","data":{"timestamp":" 947732813163"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732814894","data":{"timestamp":" 947732814893"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732816892","data":{"timestamp":" 947732816892"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732818169","data":{"timestamp":" 947732818169"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732819506","data":{"timestamp":" 947732819506"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732821178","data":{"timestamp":" 947732821178"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732822653","data":{"timestamp":" 947732822653"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" WAMEBEBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732824239","data":{"timestamp":" 947732824239"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732825390","data":{"timestamp":" 947732825390"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732826401","data":{"timestamp":" 947732826401"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732828050","data":{"timestamp":" 947732828049"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732829928","data":{"timestamp":" 947732829928"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" START_MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732831632","data":{"timestamp":" 947732831632"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732833058","data":{"timestamp":" 947732833058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732834187","data":{"timestamp":" 947732834187"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732835253","data":{"timestamp":" 947732835253"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732838874","data":{"timestamp":" 947732838874"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732839975","data":{"timestamp":" 947732839975"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732842058","data":{"timestamp":" 947732842058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732843738","data":{"timestamp":" 947732843738"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732847545","data":{"timestamp":" 947732847544"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732848660","data":{"timestamp":" 947732848660"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732851118","data":{"timestamp":" 947732851118"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732852729","data":{"timestamp":" 947732852729"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732854801","data":{"timestamp":" 947732854801"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732856346","data":{"timestamp":" 947732856346"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732858001","data":{"timestamp":" 947732858001"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732860058","data":{"timestamp":" 947732860058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732861833","data":{"timestamp":" 947732861833"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732862740","data":{"timestamp":" 947732862740"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732864338","data":{"timestamp":" 947732864338"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732866355","data":{"timestamp":" 947732866354"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732868424","data":{"timestamp":" 947732868424"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732869288","data":{"timestamp":" 947732869288"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732871495","data":{"timestamp":" 947732871495"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" MATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732873462","data":{"timestamp":" 947732873462"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732874903","data":{"timestamp":" 947732874903"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732876144","data":{"timestamp":" 947732876143"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732877210","data":{"timestamp":" 947732877210"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732879445","data":{"timestamp":" 947732879445"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732881310","data":{"timestamp":" 947732881310"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732883197","data":{"timestamp":" 947732883197"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732886563","data":{"timestamp":" 947732886563"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732888420","data":{"timestamp":" 947732888420"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732889180","data":{"timestamp":" 947732889180"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732891662","data":{"timestamp":" 947732891662"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732893397","data":{"timestamp":" 947732893396"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732894541","data":{"timestamp":" 947732894541"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732895812","data":{"timestamp":" 947732895812"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732899450","data":{"timestamp":" 947732899450"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732901430","data":{"timestamp":" 947732901429"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732903348","data":{"timestamp":" 947732903348"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732905921","data":{"timestamp":" 947732905921"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732909149","data":{"timestamp":" 947732909149"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732911099","data":{"timestamp":" 947732911098"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732912541","data":{"timestamp":" 947732912541"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732914693","data":{"timestamp":" 947732914693"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732915673","data":{"timestamp":" 947732915673"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732917402","data":{"timestamp":" 947732917402"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732918792","data":{"timestamp":" 947732918792"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732919739","data":{"timestamp":" 947732919738"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732920635","data":{"timestamp":" 947732920634"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732923306","data":{"timestamp":" 947732923306"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732927479","data":{"timestamp":" 947732927479"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIPAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732929442","data":{"timestamp":" 947732929442"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732930886","data":{"timestamp":" 947732930885"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIPAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732931996","data":{"timestamp":" 947732931995"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732932400","data":{"timestamp":" 947732932400"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" START_INAYONATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732935345","data":{"timestamp":" 947732935344"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" START_ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732937272","data":{"timestamp":" 947732937271"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732938945","data":{"timestamp":" 947732938945"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732940588","data":{"timestamp":" 947732940588"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732942040","data":{"timestamp":" 947732942040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732942424","data":{"timestamp":" 947732942424"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732945158","data":{"timestamp":" 947732945158"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732946731","data":{"timestamp":" 947732946731"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732947700","data":{"timestamp":" 947732947700"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732948637","data":{"timestamp":" 947732948636"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732949336","data":{"timestamp":" 947732949336"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732949507","data":{"timestamp":" 947732949507"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732950539","data":{"timestamp":" 947732950539"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732952214","data":{"timestamp":" 947732952214"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" START_AKACHUKUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732953412","data":{"timestamp":" 947732953411"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" AKACHUKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732955077","data":{"timestamp":" 947732955076"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGAE"," userResponse":" KIGAE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732955081","data":{"timestamp":" 947732955081"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732956785","data":{"timestamp":" 947732956784"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUNGU"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732957436","data":{"timestamp":" 947732957436"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732959126","data":{"timestamp":" 947732959126"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" KIGAE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732960792","data":{"timestamp":" 947732960791"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732960957","data":{"timestamp":" 947732960957"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732961571","data":{"timestamp":" 947732961570"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732963940","data":{"timestamp":" 947732963940"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732965349","data":{"timestamp":" 947732965349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732966526","data":{"timestamp":" 947732966526"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_ALIFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732969064","data":{"timestamp":" 947732969063"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732970658","data":{"timestamp":" 947732970656"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732971877","data":{"timestamp":" 947732971876"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732976001","data":{"timestamp":" 947732976001"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732977887","data":{"timestamp":" 947732977887"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732979739","data":{"timestamp":" 947732979739"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732982067","data":{"timestamp":" 947732982067"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732983561","data":{"timestamp":" 947732983561"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732983874","data":{"timestamp":" 947732983874"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732985781","data":{"timestamp":" 947732985780"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732987557","data":{"timestamp":" 947732987556"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732989407","data":{"timestamp":" 947732989407"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" START_NAOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732990756","data":{"timestamp":" 947732990756"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732992631","data":{"timestamp":" 947732992631"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732993465","data":{"timestamp":" 947732993464"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732995481","data":{"timestamp":" 947732995481"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732998079","data":{"timestamp":" 947732998079"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" USADIZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732999350","data":{"timestamp":" 947732999350"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733000524","data":{"timestamp":" 947733000524"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIPAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733001531","data":{"timestamp":" 947733001530"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733003121","data":{"timestamp":" 947733003121"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733005367","data":{"timestamp":" 947733005367"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733005863","data":{"timestamp":" 947733005863"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733007586","data":{"timestamp":" 947733007586"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733009064","data":{"timestamp":" 947733009064"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733011120","data":{"timestamp":" 947733011119"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" ALIJIPAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733012301","data":{"timestamp":" 947733012301"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733014290","data":{"timestamp":" 947733014289"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733015979","data":{"timestamp":" 947733015979"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733019296","data":{"timestamp":" 947733019296"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733021169","data":{"timestamp":" 947733021169"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733023946","data":{"timestamp":" 947733023946"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" START_WAKIMCHUKULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733026191","data":{"timestamp":" 947733026191"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733028329","data":{"timestamp":" 947733028328"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733028522","data":{"timestamp":" 947733028522"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733029970","data":{"timestamp":" 947733029970"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733031246","data":{"timestamp":" 947733031246"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733032867","data":{"timestamp":" 947733032867"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733034083","data":{"timestamp":" 947733034083"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733035277","data":{"timestamp":" 947733035277"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733037067","data":{"timestamp":" 947733037067"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733038693","data":{"timestamp":" 947733038693"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733038992","data":{"timestamp":" 947733038992"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733040929","data":{"timestamp":" 947733040929"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" START_KUTOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733042403","data":{"timestamp":" 947733042403"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733043689","data":{"timestamp":" 947733043689"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733045139","data":{"timestamp":" 947733045139"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733045445","data":{"timestamp":" 947733045444"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733046337","data":{"timestamp":" 947733046337"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733049665","data":{"timestamp":" 947733049665"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733051332","data":{"timestamp":" 947733051332"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733053805","data":{"timestamp":" 947733053805"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733055273","data":{"timestamp":" 947733055272"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733057265","data":{"timestamp":" 947733057265"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733058622","data":{"timestamp":" 947733058622"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733059649","data":{"timestamp":" 947733059649"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733060344","data":{"timestamp":" 947733060344"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733062027","data":{"timestamp":" 947733062026"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733063125","data":{"timestamp":" 947733063125"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733065104","data":{"timestamp":" 947733065104"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733065968","data":{"timestamp":" 947733065968"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733067459","data":{"timestamp":" 947733067459"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" START_MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733068738","data":{"timestamp":" 947733068738"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733070336","data":{"timestamp":" 947733070336"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733073064","data":{"timestamp":" 947733073063"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733074321","data":{"timestamp":" 947733074321"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733074324","data":{"timestamp":" 947733074323"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733077114","data":{"timestamp":" 947733077114"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733078503","data":{"timestamp":" 947733078503"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733080458","data":{"timestamp":" 947733080457"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733081453","data":{"timestamp":" 947733081452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733083349","data":{"timestamp":" 947733083349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733084832","data":{"timestamp":" 947733084832"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733085760","data":{"timestamp":" 947733085760"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733087035","data":{"timestamp":" 947733087035"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" MAKALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733088989","data":{"timestamp":" 947733088989"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" ALIWASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733089668","data":{"timestamp":" 947733089668"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733092081","data":{"timestamp":" 947733092081"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733095198","data":{"timestamp":" 947733095198"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733097297","data":{"timestamp":" 947733097297"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" KUHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733098012","data":{"timestamp":" 947733098012"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" LILIJINATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733099469","data":{"timestamp":" 947733099469"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733100960","data":{"timestamp":" 947733100960"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733103128","data":{"timestamp":" 947733103127"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733107093","data":{"timestamp":" 947733107093"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733108808","data":{"timestamp":" 947733108808"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733109290","data":{"timestamp":" 947733109290"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" START_LILIJINATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733112658","data":{"timestamp":" 947733112658"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733114521","data":{"timestamp":" 947733114521"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733117995","data":{"timestamp":" 947733117995"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733119686","data":{"timestamp":" 947733119686"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733120947","data":{"timestamp":" 947733120946"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733121234","data":{"timestamp":" 947733121234"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" START_JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733122873","data":{"timestamp":" 947733122873"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733124259","data":{"timestamp":" 947733124259"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733127268","data":{"timestamp":" 947733127268"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733128714","data":{"timestamp":" 947733128714"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733131634","data":{"timestamp":" 947733131634"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733134641","data":{"timestamp":" 947733134641"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733137979","data":{"timestamp":" 947733137978"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733139393","data":{"timestamp":" 947733139393"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733140413","data":{"timestamp":" 947733140413"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733142308","data":{"timestamp":" 947733142306"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733143584","data":{"timestamp":" 947733143583"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" ALIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733144288","data":{"timestamp":" 947733144287"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733146127","data":{"timestamp":" 947733146127"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733147196","data":{"timestamp":" 947733147196"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733149311","data":{"timestamp":" 947733149311"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733152081","data":{"timestamp":" 947733152080"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733154627","data":{"timestamp":" 947733154626"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733154656","data":{"timestamp":" 947733154656"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733156151","data":{"timestamp":" 947733156151"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733157818","data":{"timestamp":" 947733157818"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733160513","data":{"timestamp":" 947733160513"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733162794","data":{"timestamp":" 947733162794"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733163304","data":{"timestamp":" 947733163304"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733163901","data":{"timestamp":" 947733163901"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733166626","data":{"timestamp":" 947733166626"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733172070","data":{"timestamp":" 947733172070"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733174092","data":{"timestamp":" 947733174092"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733174858","data":{"timestamp":" 947733174858"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733175787","data":{"timestamp":" 947733175787"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733176162","data":{"timestamp":" 947733176162"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733179758","data":{"timestamp":" 947733179758"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733180566","data":{"timestamp":" 947733180566"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733183268","data":{"timestamp":" 947733183268"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733184018","data":{"timestamp":" 947733184018"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" START_WALIANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733185626","data":{"timestamp":" 947733185626"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733187060","data":{"timestamp":" 947733187060"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733187962","data":{"timestamp":" 947733187962"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733190058","data":{"timestamp":" 947733190058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733190939","data":{"timestamp":" 947733190939"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733194195","data":{"timestamp":" 947733194194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733198209","data":{"timestamp":" 947733198209"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733199957","data":{"timestamp":" 947733199957"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733201757","data":{"timestamp":" 947733201757"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733203221","data":{"timestamp":" 947733203221"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733204695","data":{"timestamp":" 947733204694"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733205968","data":{"timestamp":" 947733205968"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733206483","data":{"timestamp":" 947733206483"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733208154","data":{"timestamp":" 947733208154"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733210355","data":{"timestamp":" 947733210355"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733211153","data":{"timestamp":" 947733211153"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733211850","data":{"timestamp":" 947733211850"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733215220","data":{"timestamp":" 947733215220"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733216120","data":{"timestamp":" 947733216120"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733217110","data":{"timestamp":" 947733217110"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733218675","data":{"timestamp":" 947733218675"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733219884","data":{"timestamp":" 947733219883"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733222372","data":{"timestamp":" 947733222372"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733225583","data":{"timestamp":" 947733225583"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733227252","data":{"timestamp":" 947733227252"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733228433","data":{"timestamp":" 947733228433"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733229777","data":{"timestamp":" 947733229777"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733231280","data":{"timestamp":" 947733231279"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733233668","data":{"timestamp":" 947733233668"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733235202","data":{"timestamp":" 947733235202"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733235808","data":{"timestamp":" 947733235808"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733236696","data":{"timestamp":" 947733236695"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733238399","data":{"timestamp":" 947733238398"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733240092","data":{"timestamp":" 947733240092"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733242088","data":{"timestamp":" 947733242088"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733243978","data":{"timestamp":" 947733243978"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733245457","data":{"timestamp":" 947733245457"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733246707","data":{"timestamp":" 947733246707"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733248366","data":{"timestamp":" 947733248365"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733249116","data":{"timestamp":" 947733249116"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733249457","data":{"timestamp":" 947733249457"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733250052","data":{"timestamp":" 947733250052"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733251815","data":{"timestamp":" 947733251814"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733253786","data":{"timestamp":" 947733253786"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733255078","data":{"timestamp":" 947733255078"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733256479","data":{"timestamp":" 947733256478"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733259282","data":{"timestamp":" 947733259282"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733261113","data":{"timestamp":" 947733261113"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" START_WALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733263132","data":{"timestamp":" 947733263132"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733264941","data":{"timestamp":" 947733264941"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733265881","data":{"timestamp":" 947733265881"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733266971","data":{"timestamp":" 947733266971"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733268496","data":{"timestamp":" 947733268496"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733269687","data":{"timestamp":" 947733269687"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733270746","data":{"timestamp":" 947733270746"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733272016","data":{"timestamp":" 947733272016"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733273141","data":{"timestamp":" 947733273141"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733274738","data":{"timestamp":" 947733274738"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733274792","data":{"timestamp":" 947733274791"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733274909","data":{"timestamp":" 947733274908"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 0904c921-632c-459b-a6a2-b8230474909f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733285997","data":{"timestamp":" 947733285996"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733287651","data":{"timestamp":" 947733287651"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733297415","data":{"timestamp":" 947733297415"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733298886","data":{"timestamp":" 947733298886"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733300559","data":{"timestamp":" 947733300558"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733301723","data":{"timestamp":" 947733301722"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733302731","data":{"timestamp":" 947733302731"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733304393","data":{"timestamp":" 947733304393"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733304677","data":{"timestamp":" 947733304677"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733306000","data":{"timestamp":" 947733305999"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733307586","data":{"timestamp":" 947733307586"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733308410","data":{"timestamp":" 947733308409"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733309811","data":{"timestamp":" 947733309811"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733310270","data":{"timestamp":" 947733310270"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733312279","data":{"timestamp":" 947733312278"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733314130","data":{"timestamp":" 947733314130"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" START_KIANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733315556","data":{"timestamp":" 947733315556"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733317490","data":{"timestamp":" 947733317490"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733317663","data":{"timestamp":" 947733317663"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733318371","data":{"timestamp":" 947733318371"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733318879","data":{"timestamp":" 947733318879"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733321792","data":{"timestamp":" 947733321791"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733322985","data":{"timestamp":" 947733322985"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733324387","data":{"timestamp":" 947733324387"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733326287","data":{"timestamp":" 947733326286"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733326583","data":{"timestamp":" 947733326582"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733329691","data":{"timestamp":" 947733329690"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733330865","data":{"timestamp":" 947733330865"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733333281","data":{"timestamp":" 947733333280"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733334559","data":{"timestamp":" 947733334558"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733334761","data":{"timestamp":" 947733334761"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733338432","data":{"timestamp":" 947733338432"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733340333","data":{"timestamp":" 947733340333"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733341734","data":{"timestamp":" 947733341734"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733343270","data":{"timestamp":" 947733343270"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733345120","data":{"timestamp":" 947733345119"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733346026","data":{"timestamp":" 947733346025"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733347006","data":{"timestamp":" 947733347006"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" START_MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733348522","data":{"timestamp":" 947733348520"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733349988","data":{"timestamp":" 947733349988"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733351350","data":{"timestamp":" 947733351350"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733351669","data":{"timestamp":" 947733351669"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733352592","data":{"timestamp":" 947733352592"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733355209","data":{"timestamp":" 947733355209"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733357065","data":{"timestamp":" 947733357064"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733357367","data":{"timestamp":" 947733357367"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733361814","data":{"timestamp":" 947733361813"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733362530","data":{"timestamp":" 947733362530"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733364001","data":{"timestamp":" 947733364001"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733365724","data":{"timestamp":" 947733365724"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733366674","data":{"timestamp":" 947733366674"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733367641","data":{"timestamp":" 947733367641"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733368923","data":{"timestamp":" 947733368923"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733369737","data":{"timestamp":" 947733369737"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733371617","data":{"timestamp":" 947733371617"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" START_NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733373199","data":{"timestamp":" 947733373198"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733374373","data":{"timestamp":" 947733374372"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733376109","data":{"timestamp":" 947733376108"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733377963","data":{"timestamp":" 947733377963"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733380243","data":{"timestamp":" 947733380243"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733384150","data":{"timestamp":" 947733384150"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733385781","data":{"timestamp":" 947733385780"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733386060","data":{"timestamp":" 947733386060"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733390195","data":{"timestamp":" 947733390195"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" START_HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733391552","data":{"timestamp":" 947733391552"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733391833","data":{"timestamp":" 947733391833"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733394403","data":{"timestamp":" 947733394403"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733395879","data":{"timestamp":" 947733395879"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733397877","data":{"timestamp":" 947733397877"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733400537","data":{"timestamp":" 947733400537"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733402060","data":{"timestamp":" 947733402060"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733403472","data":{"timestamp":" 947733403472"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733405054","data":{"timestamp":" 947733405054"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733406704","data":{"timestamp":" 947733406703"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733407398","data":{"timestamp":" 947733407398"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733408444","data":{"timestamp":" 947733408444"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733409653","data":{"timestamp":" 947733409653"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733412035","data":{"timestamp":" 947733412035"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733416189","data":{"timestamp":" 947733416189"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733417838","data":{"timestamp":" 947733417838"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733421194","data":{"timestamp":" 947733421194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733423553","data":{"timestamp":" 947733423553"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733424666","data":{"timestamp":" 947733424666"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733425789","data":{"timestamp":" 947733425789"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733427392","data":{"timestamp":" 947733427392"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733436522","data":{"timestamp":" 947733436522"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" START_KUWALETEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733438214","data":{"timestamp":" 947733438213"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733440000","data":{"timestamp":" 947733439999"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733440060","data":{"timestamp":" 947733440060"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733441867","data":{"timestamp":" 947733441867"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733443500","data":{"timestamp":" 947733443499"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733447009","data":{"timestamp":" 947733447008"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733447876","data":{"timestamp":" 947733447876"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733449964","data":{"timestamp":" 947733449964"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733451827","data":{"timestamp":" 947733451827"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733452957","data":{"timestamp":" 947733452957"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" START_MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733454697","data":{"timestamp":" 947733454697"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733456067","data":{"timestamp":" 947733456067"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" MATE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733458409","data":{"timestamp":" 947733458409"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733459985","data":{"timestamp":" 947733459985"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733460981","data":{"timestamp":" 947733460981"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733463010","data":{"timestamp":" 947733463010"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733464677","data":{"timestamp":" 947733464676"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733466680","data":{"timestamp":" 947733466680"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733468698","data":{"timestamp":" 947733468697"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733471032","data":{"timestamp":" 947733471032"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" ALIDONDOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733471142","data":{"timestamp":" 947733471142"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733477963","data":{"timestamp":" 947733477962"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733485556","data":{"timestamp":" 947733485556"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733487093","data":{"timestamp":" 947733487092"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733489667","data":{"timestamp":" 947733489667"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" WAMEBEBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733493006","data":{"timestamp":" 947733493006"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" ALIPOYAONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733494256","data":{"timestamp":" 947733494256"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733495953","data":{"timestamp":" 947733495953"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733497062","data":{"timestamp":" 947733497062"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" START_ANGEWEZAJE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733498891","data":{"timestamp":" 947733498891"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733500276","data":{"timestamp":" 947733500276"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733501772","data":{"timestamp":" 947733501772"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733503580","data":{"timestamp":" 947733503580"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733505541","data":{"timestamp":" 947733505541"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733507401","data":{"timestamp":" 947733507401"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733508876","data":{"timestamp":" 947733508876"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733510459","data":{"timestamp":" 947733510458"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733512085","data":{"timestamp":" 947733512085"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733512897","data":{"timestamp":" 947733512897"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" START_ALIFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733514742","data":{"timestamp":" 947733514742"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733517613","data":{"timestamp":" 947733517613"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733520402","data":{"timestamp":" 947733520401"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733522378","data":{"timestamp":" 947733522377"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733522671","data":{"timestamp":" 947733522670"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733523444","data":{"timestamp":" 947733523444"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733529113","data":{"timestamp":" 947733529112"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733533376","data":{"timestamp":" 947733533376"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" AKAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733533392","data":{"timestamp":" 947733533392"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733534142","data":{"timestamp":" 947733534142"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733535230","data":{"timestamp":" 947733535229"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733536786","data":{"timestamp":" 947733536786"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733540379","data":{"timestamp":" 947733540379"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733542254","data":{"timestamp":" 947733542254"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733544198","data":{"timestamp":" 947733544197"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733544883","data":{"timestamp":" 947733544883"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733546600","data":{"timestamp":" 947733546600"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733550625","data":{"timestamp":" 947733550625"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733552521","data":{"timestamp":" 947733552521"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733555980","data":{"timestamp":" 947733555980"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733559131","data":{"timestamp":" 947733559131"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" START_SEHEMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733562293","data":{"timestamp":" 947733562293"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733563905","data":{"timestamp":" 947733563905"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733564508","data":{"timestamp":" 947733564508"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" INAYONATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733568701","data":{"timestamp":" 947733568701"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733570781","data":{"timestamp":" 947733570781"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733571102","data":{"timestamp":" 947733571102"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733572378","data":{"timestamp":" 947733572378"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733574501","data":{"timestamp":" 947733574501"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733576024","data":{"timestamp":" 947733576023"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733576313","data":{"timestamp":" 947733576312"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733582622","data":{"timestamp":" 947733582622"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" START_AKACHUKUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733585112","data":{"timestamp":" 947733585111"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733595102","data":{"timestamp":" 947733595102"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIGAE"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733597720","data":{"timestamp":" 947733597720"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIGAE"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733599196","data":{"timestamp":" 947733599195"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGAE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733601690","data":{"timestamp":" 947733601690"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" START_INAYONATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733604637","data":{"timestamp":" 947733604637"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733607051","data":{"timestamp":" 947733607051"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUNGU"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733608508","data":{"timestamp":" 947733608507"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733609415","data":{"timestamp":" 947733609414"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" START_INAYONATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733611287","data":{"timestamp":" 947733611287"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733612255","data":{"timestamp":" 947733612255"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733614615","data":{"timestamp":" 947733614615"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733615251","data":{"timestamp":" 947733615251"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733616775","data":{"timestamp":" 947733616775"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733617930","data":{"timestamp":" 947733617930"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733618706","data":{"timestamp":" 947733618706"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733622460","data":{"timestamp":" 947733622459"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733623453","data":{"timestamp":" 947733623452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733640305","data":{"timestamp":" 947733640305"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733642125","data":{"timestamp":" 947733642125"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USADIZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733647486","data":{"timestamp":" 947733647486"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733648714","data":{"timestamp":" 947733648714"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733650393","data":{"timestamp":" 947733650393"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733650397","data":{"timestamp":" 947733650397"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733650402","data":{"timestamp":" 947733650402"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naomba kaa la moto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733653785","data":{"timestamp":" 947733653784"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733654555","data":{"timestamp":" 947733654555"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733655538","data":{"timestamp":" 947733655538"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733657229","data":{"timestamp":" 947733657229"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733658958","data":{"timestamp":" 947733658958"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733660992","data":{"timestamp":" 947733660991"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jiko langu limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733663054","data":{"timestamp":" 947733663054"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733664387","data":{"timestamp":" 947733664386"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733666278","data":{"timestamp":" 947733666278"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733667462","data":{"timestamp":" 947733667462"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733669605","data":{"timestamp":" 947733669605"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733671725","data":{"timestamp":" 947733671724"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMCHUKULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733673913","data":{"timestamp":" 947733673913"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" NYUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733676186","data":{"timestamp":" 947733676185"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733677549","data":{"timestamp":" 947733677549"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733678943","data":{"timestamp":" 947733678943"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" START_TAFADHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733702150","data":{"timestamp":" 947733702150"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733703650","data":{"timestamp":" 947733703650"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733704179","data":{"timestamp":" 947733704179"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733706090","data":{"timestamp":" 947733706090"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733707594","data":{"timestamp":" 947733707593"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733708779","data":{"timestamp":" 947733708779"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733710512","data":{"timestamp":" 947733710512"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733711894","data":{"timestamp":" 947733711893"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733712664","data":{"timestamp":" 947733712664"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733714607","data":{"timestamp":" 947733714607"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733715495","data":{"timestamp":" 947733715495"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733718507","data":{"timestamp":" 947733718507"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733719382","data":{"timestamp":" 947733719382"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733721395","data":{"timestamp":" 947733721395"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733722868","data":{"timestamp":" 947733722868"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733725769","data":{"timestamp":" 947733725769"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733725774","data":{"timestamp":" 947733725774"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733730391","data":{"timestamp":" 947733730391"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733731856","data":{"timestamp":" 947733731856"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733734486","data":{"timestamp":" 947733734486"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733736002","data":{"timestamp":" 947733736002"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733737800","data":{"timestamp":" 947733737800"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakimchukulia kaa la moto kutoka kwenye jiko Anansi alikalia tunda moja kubwa la mkuyu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733740267","data":{"timestamp":" 947733740267"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733741098","data":{"timestamp":" 947733741098"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733743393","data":{"timestamp":" 947733743393"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733744827","data":{"timestamp":" 947733744827"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733745480","data":{"timestamp":" 947733745480"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIJINATA"," userResponse":" LILIJINATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733745910","data":{"timestamp":" 947733745910"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733748864","data":{"timestamp":" 947733748864"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733750291","data":{"timestamp":" 947733750291"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733750594","data":{"timestamp":" 947733750593"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733753994","data":{"timestamp":" 947733753994"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" START_INAYONATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733755789","data":{"timestamp":" 947733755789"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunda hilo lilijinata kwenye makalio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALIO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733760812","data":{"timestamp":" 947733760812"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" KUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733764178","data":{"timestamp":" 947733764178"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" START_ALIWASHUKURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733766220","data":{"timestamp":" 947733766220"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASHUKURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733775287","data":{"timestamp":" 947733775287"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733775291","data":{"timestamp":" 947733775291"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733783796","data":{"timestamp":" 947733783796"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" KUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733789675","data":{"timestamp":" 947733789675"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" LIMEZIMIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733791477","data":{"timestamp":" 947733791477"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733794591","data":{"timestamp":" 947733794591"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733807491","data":{"timestamp":" 947733807490"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733808992","data":{"timestamp":" 947733808992"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733812680","data":{"timestamp":" 947733812680"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733814650","data":{"timestamp":" 947733814649"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733816366","data":{"timestamp":" 947733816366"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733820656","data":{"timestamp":" 947733820656"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733822558","data":{"timestamp":" 947733822558"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733824426","data":{"timestamp":" 947733824426"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733835955","data":{"timestamp":" 947733835955"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733856942","data":{"timestamp":" 947733856942"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" KUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733856946","data":{"timestamp":" 947733856945"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwashukuru kunguru na kuharakisha kwenda nyumbani kufurahia kuyu hilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733867368","data":{"timestamp":" 947733867368"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733867885","data":{"timestamp":" 947733867884"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733868268","data":{"timestamp":" 947733868268"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733869800","data":{"timestamp":" 947733869800"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733875145","data":{"timestamp":" 947733875145"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733877030","data":{"timestamp":" 947733877030"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733878852","data":{"timestamp":" 947733878852"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" ALIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733879012","data":{"timestamp":" 947733879012"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733880729","data":{"timestamp":" 947733880729"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" HALIKUTOSHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733882967","data":{"timestamp":" 947733882967"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733885470","data":{"timestamp":" 947733885470"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733887013","data":{"timestamp":" 947733887013"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733888348","data":{"timestamp":" 947733888348"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733893925","data":{"timestamp":" 947733893925"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733896857","data":{"timestamp":" 947733896857"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733896861","data":{"timestamp":" 947733896861"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" AKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733896871","data":{"timestamp":" 947733896871"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733897738","data":{"timestamp":" 947733897737"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733898511","data":{"timestamp":" 947733898511"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733900237","data":{"timestamp":" 947733900237"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733903820","data":{"timestamp":" 947733903820"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733904971","data":{"timestamp":" 947733904971"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733906280","data":{"timestamp":" 947733906279"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733908143","data":{"timestamp":" 947733908143"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733910850","data":{"timestamp":" 947733910850"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733913685","data":{"timestamp":" 947733913685"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733915699","data":{"timestamp":" 947733915699"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733916841","data":{"timestamp":" 947733916841"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" AKAFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733921456","data":{"timestamp":" 947733921456"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733932116","data":{"timestamp":" 947733932116"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733979490","data":{"timestamp":" 947733979490"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734022002","data":{"timestamp":" 947734022002"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734091452","data":{"timestamp":" 947734091452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734091758","data":{"timestamp":" 947734091758"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734097184","data":{"timestamp":" 947734097184"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734098985","data":{"timestamp":" 947734098985"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734100593","data":{"timestamp":" 947734100592"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734100959","data":{"timestamp":" 947734100958"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734102459","data":{"timestamp":" 947734102459"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734104067","data":{"timestamp":" 947734104067"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734105218","data":{"timestamp":" 947734105217"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734106570","data":{"timestamp":" 947734106570"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734107792","data":{"timestamp":" 947734107792"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734108482","data":{"timestamp":" 947734108482"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" AKAFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734109643","data":{"timestamp":" 947734109643"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734110709","data":{"timestamp":" 947734110709"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" UNARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734113262","data":{"timestamp":" 947734113262"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734114347","data":{"timestamp":" 947734114347"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734115836","data":{"timestamp":" 947734115835"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734116423","data":{"timestamp":" 947734116422"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734117651","data":{"timestamp":" 947734117651"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734118072","data":{"timestamp":" 947734118072"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734120565","data":{"timestamp":" 947734120565"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734122149","data":{"timestamp":" 947734122149"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734123583","data":{"timestamp":" 947734123583"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734123852","data":{"timestamp":" 947734123852"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734126802","data":{"timestamp":" 947734126802"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734129135","data":{"timestamp":" 947734129134"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734131622","data":{"timestamp":" 947734131622"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734133564","data":{"timestamp":" 947734133564"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734139916","data":{"timestamp":" 947734139916"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734155164","data":{"timestamp":" 947734155163"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734158018","data":{"timestamp":" 947734158018"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734170330","data":{"timestamp":" 947734170330"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734174250","data":{"timestamp":" 947734174250"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734175797","data":{"timestamp":" 947734175797"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734178500","data":{"timestamp":" 947734178500"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734189373","data":{"timestamp":" 947734189373"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" START_NIKIFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734190660","data":{"timestamp":" 947734190660"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734197532","data":{"timestamp":" 947734197532"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734200570","data":{"timestamp":" 947734200570"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734201699","data":{"timestamp":" 947734201699"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734204106","data":{"timestamp":" 947734204106"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734206005","data":{"timestamp":" 947734206004"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734207389","data":{"timestamp":" 947734207389"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734212601","data":{"timestamp":" 947734212600"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734214303","data":{"timestamp":" 947734214302"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734220706","data":{"timestamp":" 947734220706"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734225550","data":{"timestamp":" 947734225550"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734226903","data":{"timestamp":" 947734226902"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734233387","data":{"timestamp":" 947734233386"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734234800","data":{"timestamp":" 947734234800"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734241387","data":{"timestamp":" 947734241387"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734244557","data":{"timestamp":" 947734244557"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734247071","data":{"timestamp":" 947734247071"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734249598","data":{"timestamp":" 947734249598"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734252187","data":{"timestamp":" 947734252187"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734256212","data":{"timestamp":" 947734256212"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734266200","data":{"timestamp":" 947734266200"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734271208","data":{"timestamp":" 947734271208"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734276305","data":{"timestamp":" 947734276305"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734278058","data":{"timestamp":" 947734278058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734286060","data":{"timestamp":" 947734286060"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734288122","data":{"timestamp":" 947734288122"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734289386","data":{"timestamp":" 947734289386"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734290440","data":{"timestamp":" 947734290440"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734292901","data":{"timestamp":" 947734292901"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734294163","data":{"timestamp":" 947734294163"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734294988","data":{"timestamp":" 947734294988"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734300397","data":{"timestamp":" 947734300396"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734302076","data":{"timestamp":" 947734302075"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734305277","data":{"timestamp":" 947734305277"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734307445","data":{"timestamp":" 947734307445"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734309289","data":{"timestamp":" 947734309289"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734313246","data":{"timestamp":" 947734313246"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734316575","data":{"timestamp":" 947734316574"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734321314","data":{"timestamp":" 947734321314"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734325713","data":{"timestamp":" 947734325713"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734327050","data":{"timestamp":" 947734327050"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734327582","data":{"timestamp":" 947734327582"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734333985","data":{"timestamp":" 947734333985"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734338484","data":{"timestamp":" 947734338484"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734345077","data":{"timestamp":" 947734345077"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734349166","data":{"timestamp":" 947734349165"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734350492","data":{"timestamp":" 947734350491"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734353990","data":{"timestamp":" 947734353990"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734356157","data":{"timestamp":" 947734356157"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" NIKIFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734358139","data":{"timestamp":" 947734358138"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734359312","data":{"timestamp":" 947734359312"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" HURUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734361656","data":{"timestamp":" 947734361656"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734363275","data":{"timestamp":" 947734363274"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734367427","data":{"timestamp":" 947734367427"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734368998","data":{"timestamp":" 947734368998"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEBA"," userResponse":" BEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734370105","data":{"timestamp":" 947734370105"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734373427","data":{"timestamp":" 947734373427"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734373431","data":{"timestamp":" 947734373431"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINGINE"," userResponse":" JINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734373436","data":{"timestamp":" 947734373436"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734374930","data":{"timestamp":" 947734374930"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734375639","data":{"timestamp":" 947734375639"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734377025","data":{"timestamp":" 947734377025"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734378394","data":{"timestamp":" 947734378394"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734384189","data":{"timestamp":" 947734384188"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734386122","data":{"timestamp":" 947734386122"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" START_MAPEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734387585","data":{"timestamp":" 947734387585"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734389945","data":{"timestamp":" 947734389945"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734394873","data":{"timestamp":" 947734394872"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734396757","data":{"timestamp":" 947734396757"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734397522","data":{"timestamp":" 947734397522"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAENDA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734401044","data":{"timestamp":" 947734401044"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734404148","data":{"timestamp":" 947734404148"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734410372","data":{"timestamp":" 947734410372"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734412751","data":{"timestamp":" 947734412750"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734412762","data":{"timestamp":" 947734412762"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734428168","data":{"timestamp":" 947734428167"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734434496","data":{"timestamp":" 947734434496"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734437683","data":{"timestamp":" 947734437683"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734439567","data":{"timestamp":" 947734439567"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734441606","data":{"timestamp":" 947734441606"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734443441","data":{"timestamp":" 947734443441"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734445591","data":{"timestamp":" 947734445591"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734447376","data":{"timestamp":" 947734447376"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734451197","data":{"timestamp":" 947734451197"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734452733","data":{"timestamp":" 947734452733"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734453856","data":{"timestamp":" 947734453855"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHANGIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734455513","data":{"timestamp":" 947734455513"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734457510","data":{"timestamp":" 947734457510"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734459622","data":{"timestamp":" 947734459621"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734462982","data":{"timestamp":" 947734462981"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734469811","data":{"timestamp":" 947734469811"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734471299","data":{"timestamp":" 947734471299"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734472982","data":{"timestamp":" 947734472982"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734480524","data":{"timestamp":" 947734480523"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734482260","data":{"timestamp":" 947734482260"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734485231","data":{"timestamp":" 947734485231"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734487876","data":{"timestamp":" 947734487876"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734489332","data":{"timestamp":" 947734489331"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734490931","data":{"timestamp":" 947734490931"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734493035","data":{"timestamp":" 947734493034"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734494641","data":{"timestamp":" 947734494641"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734495784","data":{"timestamp":" 947734495784"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734497275","data":{"timestamp":" 947734497275"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" AKARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734497981","data":{"timestamp":" 947734497981"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734497985","data":{"timestamp":" 947734497985"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734504456","data":{"timestamp":" 947734504456"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734506702","data":{"timestamp":" 947734506702"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734509657","data":{"timestamp":" 947734509657"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734512294","data":{"timestamp":" 947734512294"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734514187","data":{"timestamp":" 947734514186"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734515779","data":{"timestamp":" 947734515779"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734518916","data":{"timestamp":" 947734518916"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734519800","data":{"timestamp":" 947734519800"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734520713","data":{"timestamp":" 947734520713"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHANGIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734522083","data":{"timestamp":" 947734522083"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734523228","data":{"timestamp":" 947734523228"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONA"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734525679","data":{"timestamp":" 947734525678"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734527559","data":{"timestamp":" 947734527558"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734530237","data":{"timestamp":" 947734530237"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734532080","data":{"timestamp":" 947734532079"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734533571","data":{"timestamp":" 947734533571"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734533753","data":{"timestamp":" 947734533753"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734535847","data":{"timestamp":" 947734535847"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734537807","data":{"timestamp":" 947734537807"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734539870","data":{"timestamp":" 947734539869"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734542046","data":{"timestamp":" 947734542046"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHANGIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734543257","data":{"timestamp":" 947734543257"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734544657","data":{"timestamp":" 947734544657"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734546126","data":{"timestamp":" 947734546125"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734547666","data":{"timestamp":" 947734547666"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734549022","data":{"timestamp":" 947734549021"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734551401","data":{"timestamp":" 947734551401"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734553048","data":{"timestamp":" 947734553048"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734554501","data":{"timestamp":" 947734554501"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734556580","data":{"timestamp":" 947734556580"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AKARUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734559481","data":{"timestamp":" 947734559481"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KUCHUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734560740","data":{"timestamp":" 947734560739"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734563048","data":{"timestamp":" 947734563048"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734564520","data":{"timestamp":" 947734564520"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734566196","data":{"timestamp":" 947734566195"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734568686","data":{"timestamp":" 947734568686"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734570781","data":{"timestamp":" 947734570781"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734571709","data":{"timestamp":" 947734571709"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734573457","data":{"timestamp":" 947734573457"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734575678","data":{"timestamp":" 947734575678"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734578059","data":{"timestamp":" 947734578059"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUMA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734579646","data":{"timestamp":" 947734579646"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUMA"," userResponse":" KUCHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734581350","data":{"timestamp":" 947734581350"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734583681","data":{"timestamp":" 947734583681"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734585699","data":{"timestamp":" 947734585698"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734587290","data":{"timestamp":" 947734587290"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734590441","data":{"timestamp":" 947734590441"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" START_ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734592253","data":{"timestamp":" 947734592253"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734594003","data":{"timestamp":" 947734594002"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734596085","data":{"timestamp":" 947734596085"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734597678","data":{"timestamp":" 947734597678"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734600061","data":{"timestamp":" 947734600061"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734602939","data":{"timestamp":" 947734602939"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734603834","data":{"timestamp":" 947734603834"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734605662","data":{"timestamp":" 947734605662"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734610051","data":{"timestamp":" 947734610051"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIONA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734613900","data":{"timestamp":" 947734613900"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734615228","data":{"timestamp":" 947734615228"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734617336","data":{"timestamp":" 947734617336"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734621936","data":{"timestamp":" 947734621936"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734623887","data":{"timestamp":" 947734623887"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734623977","data":{"timestamp":" 947734623977"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" START_ALICHUKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734630475","data":{"timestamp":" 947734630475"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734636013","data":{"timestamp":" 947734636012"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734637718","data":{"timestamp":" 947734637718"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWEKA"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734639680","data":{"timestamp":" 947734639680"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWEKA"," userResponse":" KULIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734646757","data":{"timestamp":" 947734646756"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734658739","data":{"timestamp":" 947734658739"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734658743","data":{"timestamp":" 947734658743"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734659270","data":{"timestamp":" 947734659270"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734659276","data":{"timestamp":" 947734659276"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734661970","data":{"timestamp":" 947734661970"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734662968","data":{"timestamp":" 947734662967"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" START_HATIMAYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734664702","data":{"timestamp":" 947734664702"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734669284","data":{"timestamp":" 947734669284"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" START_KULIWEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734671399","data":{"timestamp":" 947734671399"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734673405","data":{"timestamp":" 947734673405"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734673607","data":{"timestamp":" 947734673607"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734677120","data":{"timestamp":" 947734677120"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734678846","data":{"timestamp":" 947734678845"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734681121","data":{"timestamp":" 947734681121"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734682352","data":{"timestamp":" 947734682352"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734683750","data":{"timestamp":" 947734683750"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734685148","data":{"timestamp":" 947734685148"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734687788","data":{"timestamp":" 947734687787"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NILILIONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734689186","data":{"timestamp":" 947734689186"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734689482","data":{"timestamp":" 947734689482"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734691688","data":{"timestamp":" 947734691688"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734693161","data":{"timestamp":" 947734693161"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUPATA"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734698197","data":{"timestamp":" 947734698197"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUPATA"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734700167","data":{"timestamp":" 947734700167"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734703751","data":{"timestamp":" 947734703751"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734705237","data":{"timestamp":" 947734705237"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734707021","data":{"timestamp":" 947734707020"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye alichukuwa matunda yote na kunguru hawakupata chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734708707","data":{"timestamp":" 947734708707"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734709385","data":{"timestamp":" 947734709385"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734712563","data":{"timestamp":" 947734712563"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734718394","data":{"timestamp":" 947734718394"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734722397","data":{"timestamp":" 947734722397"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAANZA"," userResponse":" LIKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734723528","data":{"timestamp":" 947734723528"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliachwa peke yake giza likaanza kutanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTANDA"," userResponse":" KUTANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734724822","data":{"timestamp":" 947734724821"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734727996","data":{"timestamp":" 947734727996"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" SIWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734727999","data":{"timestamp":" 947734727999"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734729306","data":{"timestamp":" 947734729306"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734730205","data":{"timestamp":" 947734730205"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734730956","data":{"timestamp":" 947734730956"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734732070","data":{"timestamp":" 947734732069"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734733354","data":{"timestamp":" 947734733354"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734736947","data":{"timestamp":" 947734736947"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734737380","data":{"timestamp":" 947734737380"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734738833","data":{"timestamp":" 947734738832"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734740237","data":{"timestamp":" 947734740236"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734748900","data":{"timestamp":" 947734748900"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIAMBIA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734752797","data":{"timestamp":" 947734752797"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIAMBIA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734754761","data":{"timestamp":" 947734754761"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734757323","data":{"timestamp":" 947734757323"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734759339","data":{"timestamp":" 947734759339"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734763882","data":{"timestamp":" 947734763882"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734765742","data":{"timestamp":" 947734765742"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734765747","data":{"timestamp":" 947734765747"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIRUKE"," userResponse":" NIRUKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734766349","data":{"timestamp":" 947734766349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWANI"," userResponse":" HEWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734767759","data":{"timestamp":" 947734767759"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" HEWANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734770581","data":{"timestamp":" 947734770581"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734772042","data":{"timestamp":" 947734772042"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734775134","data":{"timestamp":" 947734775133"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734779243","data":{"timestamp":" 947734779243"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siwezi kuishi kwenye huu mti maisha yangu yote alijiambia ni lazima niruke hewani kama kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734784759","data":{"timestamp":" 947734784758"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734790663","data":{"timestamp":" 947734790663"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734792282","data":{"timestamp":" 947734792281"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734796346","data":{"timestamp":" 947734796346"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHUSHA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734797841","data":{"timestamp":" 947734797841"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHUSHA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734799671","data":{"timestamp":" 947734799671"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHUSHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734802172","data":{"timestamp":" 947734802172"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PUMZI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734806258","data":{"timestamp":" 947734806258"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUMZI"," userResponse":" PUMZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734809055","data":{"timestamp":" 947734809054"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734814935","data":{"timestamp":" 947734814935"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734816725","data":{"timestamp":" 947734816725"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734818570","data":{"timestamp":" 947734818570"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734820240","data":{"timestamp":" 947734820240"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734822984","data":{"timestamp":" 947734822984"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" LIKAANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734824410","data":{"timestamp":" 947734824409"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734825371","data":{"timestamp":" 947734825371"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734826865","data":{"timestamp":" 947734826865"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" HEWANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734828257","data":{"timestamp":" 947734828257"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734832316","data":{"timestamp":" 947734832316"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" START_AKAANGUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734843722","data":{"timestamp":" 947734843722"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" SIWEZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734845674","data":{"timestamp":" 947734845674"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734849538","data":{"timestamp":" 947734849538"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734851280","data":{"timestamp":" 947734851280"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734855221","data":{"timestamp":" 947734855221"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734855332","data":{"timestamp":" 947734855332"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734857382","data":{"timestamp":" 947734857382"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734859716","data":{"timestamp":" 947734859716"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734861177","data":{"timestamp":" 947734861177"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734861679","data":{"timestamp":" 947734861679"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734864105","data":{"timestamp":" 947734864105"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734866086","data":{"timestamp":" 947734866086"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734867901","data":{"timestamp":" 947734867900"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" KUTANDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734870318","data":{"timestamp":" 947734870317"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaanguka ndani ya mto baina ya mamba hatari."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734872293","data":{"timestamp":" 947734872293"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" NYORORO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734873831","data":{"timestamp":" 947734873831"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734875317","data":{"timestamp":" 947734875317"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734875618","data":{"timestamp":" 947734875618"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNA"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734892849","data":{"timestamp":" 947734892849"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNA"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734892853","data":{"timestamp":" 947734892853"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734896506","data":{"timestamp":" 947734896506"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMU"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734896697","data":{"timestamp":" 947734896697"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734924924","data":{"timestamp":" 947734924924"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYORORO"," userResponse":" NYORORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734939573","data":{"timestamp":" 947734939573"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734957678","data":{"timestamp":" 947734957678"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735014716","data":{"timestamp":" 947735014716"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735017744","data":{"timestamp":" 947735017744"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735027912","data":{"timestamp":" 947735027912"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735030299","data":{"timestamp":" 947735030299"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUANZE"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735031040","data":{"timestamp":" 947735031040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUANZE"," userResponse":" TUANZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735031743","data":{"timestamp":" 947735031743"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735032009","data":{"timestamp":" 947735032008"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuanze mlo mm..."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MM"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735033135","data":{"timestamp":" 947735033135"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735034157","data":{"timestamp":" 947735034157"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735036078","data":{"timestamp":" 947735036077"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735041879","data":{"timestamp":" 947735041879"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSINIUE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735045775","data":{"timestamp":" 947735045775"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MSINIUE"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735047585","data":{"timestamp":" 947735047584"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSINIUE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735053675","data":{"timestamp":" 947735053675"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735056753","data":{"timestamp":" 947735056753"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" MSINIUE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735058417","data":{"timestamp":" 947735058417"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735062716","data":{"timestamp":" 947735062716"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735066068","data":{"timestamp":" 947735066067"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali msiniue Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735067171","data":{"timestamp":" 947735067171"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735069997","data":{"timestamp":" 947735069997"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735071528","data":{"timestamp":" 947735071528"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735072671","data":{"timestamp":" 947735072671"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735074981","data":{"timestamp":" 947735074980"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735076831","data":{"timestamp":" 947735076831"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735077523","data":{"timestamp":" 947735077523"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735079471","data":{"timestamp":" 947735079471"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735080889","data":{"timestamp":" 947735080889"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735081949","data":{"timestamp":" 947735081949"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735083261","data":{"timestamp":" 947735083261"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAMJUI"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735085347","data":{"timestamp":" 947735085347"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMJUI"," userResponse":" HAMJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735085980","data":{"timestamp":" 947735085979"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735086387","data":{"timestamp":" 947735086386"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735086886","data":{"timestamp":" 947735086886"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735088662","data":{"timestamp":" 947735088662"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENU"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735089651","data":{"timestamp":" 947735089650"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani hamjui mimi ni mmoja wenu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENU"," userResponse":" WENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735091257","data":{"timestamp":" 947735091257"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOTEA"," userResponse":" HAMJUI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735094903","data":{"timestamp":" 947735094903"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOTEA"," userResponse":" TUANZE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735096813","data":{"timestamp":" 947735096813"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOTEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735103207","data":{"timestamp":" 947735103207"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735111234","data":{"timestamp":" 947735111234"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735111238","data":{"timestamp":" 947735111238"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735112892","data":{"timestamp":" 947735112892"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735145707","data":{"timestamp":" 947735145707"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" START_MABABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735147269","data":{"timestamp":" 947735147268"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735153459","data":{"timestamp":" 947735153459"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZENU"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735154524","data":{"timestamp":" 947735154524"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZENU"," userResponse":" ZENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735155482","data":{"timestamp":" 947735155482"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" HAMJUI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735162180","data":{"timestamp":" 947735162180"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735171507","data":{"timestamp":" 947735171507"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735186544","data":{"timestamp":" 947735186544"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735188144","data":{"timestamp":" 947735188143"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735194412","data":{"timestamp":" 947735194411"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735196445","data":{"timestamp":" 947735196445"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735200684","data":{"timestamp":" 947735200683"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPATA"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735218226","data":{"timestamp":" 947735218226"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPATA"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735219920","data":{"timestamp":" 947735219919"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735225633","data":{"timestamp":" 947735225632"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" MM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735232067","data":{"timestamp":" 947735232067"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735242152","data":{"timestamp":" 947735242152"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYINYI"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735252025","data":{"timestamp":" 947735252025"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINYI"," userResponse":" NYINYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735252029","data":{"timestamp":" 947735252029"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735252038","data":{"timestamp":" 947735252038"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735252045","data":{"timestamp":" 947735252045"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nyinyi ni ndugu zangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735254578","data":{"timestamp":" 947735254578"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735255395","data":{"timestamp":" 947735255395"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHOZI"," userResponse":" MACHOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735257676","data":{"timestamp":" 947735257676"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735258959","data":{"timestamp":" 947735258959"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735271401","data":{"timestamp":" 947735271400"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735283800","data":{"timestamp":" 947735283800"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735298088","data":{"timestamp":" 947735298088"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735304290","data":{"timestamp":" 947735304290"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735309771","data":{"timestamp":" 947735309771"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alilia machozi hadi mamba wakamwonea huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735315224","data":{"timestamp":" 947735315223"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735319533","data":{"timestamp":" 947735319533"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000112_055156"," gameId":" 69b872e1-ada1-46c9-a22e-bb6aeac170cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mamba mzee hakuamini Tutajua kwamba wewe ni mmoja wetu ukiweza kunywa supu ya matope kama sisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}